[Music]
[Música]
has
ha
in
en
[Music]
[Música]
H
H
P [Music]
P
P [Music] [Music]
P
Oh [Music]
Oh
Happy New Year to my kids How
Feliz año nuevo a mi chavalería Cómo
are you Happy New Year
estáis Feliz año
Happy New Year Okay How are you
nuevo Feliz año nuevo bueno Cómo estáis
guys How are you Okay let's see I've come
chicos Cómo estáis bueno a ver vengo
straight from the other live I've been
directamente del otro directo
touring the
llevo llevo todo el día recorriendo la
Iberian Peninsula all day I mean
Península ibérica o sea
literally I literally came
literalmente literalmente me he venido
from the other side of the country to here
desde la otra punta del país hasta aquí
straight to the desk Okay Ah I
directo al escritorio bueno Ah me he
took a shower and I had dinner first I have to
pegado una ducha y he cenado primero el
fix the color a little no
color lo tengo que arreglar un poco no
the color is so-so let's see I
el color está regulinchi a ver yo
would take off the spotlight today because I'm a
quitaría el foco hoy porque estoy un
little tired also I tell you not from the
poco cansado también te digo no del
trip and all I'm not going to leave it like this I'm going to
viaje y tal No lo voy a dejar así lo voy
leave it like this  a little softer because I don't really feel like being
a dejar así más flojito porque es que no
in the spotlight But anyway, I'm not
tengo muchas ganas de foco Pero bueno no
going to tell you about my trip or anything like that
os voy a contar mi viaje ni nada por el
Because I was already on telesalseo
estilo Porque ya estuve en telesalseo
commenting And telling every day if
comentando Y contando cada día si a
anyone is interested well You
alguien le interesa pues Siempre os
can always go there Anyway, you know
podéis ir para allá Igualmente ya sabéis
that man the ideal, the ideal ideals imo
que hombre lo ideal lo ideal ideals imo
is that you all follow me and are
es que todos me sigáis y me estéis
following me both on Twitter and
siguiendo tanto en Twitter como en en
everywhere else Well let's see on the street no, it
todas partes bueno a ver por la calle no
looks a little weird We've already
que queda un poco raro Ya lo hemos
talked about it on many occasions
hablado en un montón de ocasiones
and that you follow me on Instagram that you
y que me sigáis en instagram que me
follow me here we are all the well
sigáis en aquí estamos todos los bueno
all the members no I haven't checked them do you
todos los miembros no no los he revisado
want us to update that bar to see
queréis que actualicemos esa barra a ver
how much it has gone down in these days because
cuánto ha bajado en estos días porque
obviously it goes down of course let's see
obviamente baja claro a ver
eh obviously it goes
eh obviamente
down
baja
1675 members I'm not going to touch it because
1675 miembros no la voy a tocar porque
I'm too lazy to get into changing it And they
me da pereza meterme a cambiarla Y no
are not that many but Uf
son tanto pero Uf
1675 members what times those eh in which
1675 miembros qué tiempos aquellos eh en
the kids were capable
los que la chavalería eran capaces
of reaching 3000 members and those
de de llegar a 3000 miembros y esas
atrocities eh What times those were
barbaridades eh Qué tiempo aquellos
now the ones who pull are the  of the ones from the
ahora los que tiran son los de los de la
telesalseo
los del telesalseo
now the ones who throw are the ones from the
ahora los que tiran son los del
telesalseo it
telesalseo
would have been cool a photo with Roma
hubiera molado una foto con Roma
Gallardo but the thing is that Roma Gallardo doesn't
Gallardo pero es que Roma Gallardo no
live there no I mean it's just that I was afraid to
vive allí no o sea es que me daba cosa
talk to anyone at the end of the year I spoke with
hablarle a nadie en fin de año hablé con
well I spoke with these people because I speak
bueno hablé con esta gente porque hablo
every day in the end with Marina and with
todos los días al final con Marina y con
Alanne well it's rare the day that I don't speak
alanne pues raro es el día que no hablo
especially with Alanne but Alanne yes or
sobre todo con alanne pero alanne sí o
yes I don't have to let her know that I'm
sí no la tengo que avisar que estoy
close but with Roma Gallardo neither do
cerca pero a Roma Gallardo tampoco tengo
I. Let's see he's a colleague he's a good
yo un A ver es un colega es un buen
friend the truth is he's a little friend he's a
amigo la verdad es un coleguita es un
good friend
buen amigo
eh but I don't have a daily relationship with him
eh pero no tengo una relación con él de
we talk from time to time and well
diario hablamos de vez en cuando y bueno
surely Maybe yes yes I
seguramente A lo mejor si si le hubiera
would have told him once in a while no maybe we could have hang out for
dicho de vez no a lo mejor podíamos
a while but I don't like
haber quear un rato pero no me gusta
calling people when I go with
estar llamando a la gente cuando voy con
the family when I go with the family
la familia cuando voy con con la familia
no I don't like calling anyone You
no no me gusta estar llamando a nadie
know because I go with the kids you know I go
Sabes porque voy con los niños sabes Voy
differently no I don't know if the quality but yes
diferente no no sé si la calidad pero si
the quality goes down the rest
la calidad baja lo demás
too Rocío this doesn't work like that queen
también Rocío esto no funciona así reina
in  telesalseo are the ones who maintain, or
en telesalseo son los que mantienen o
rather, the ones who pull the cart right now, they
sea los que tiran del carro ahora mismo
are the
son la
gentlemen. The live show began there
señoreros comenzaba por allí el directo
before, look how happy they have me
antes fijaros lo contento que me tienen
and you guys. Well, it's not that you
y a ustedes Pues bueno no es que me
have me out of context. But well,
tengáis en descontexto Pero bueno
some of you, a little bit, yes, aas, most likely I'll see it
algunos algunos un poco sí aas muy
soon, I can't
probablemente lo veo pronto no os puedo
tell you why, but I'll see it very soon,
decir por qué pero lo veo muy pronto
probably we want some
probablemente queremos algo de
windy. Well, delox sent that to Luchi, a
windy Pues eso lo manda delox luchi un
kiss, two months, yes, a kiss, a kiss, Luchi.
beso dos mesec yos un beso un beso luchi
Javi, you have to see Susi's live show. We'll
Javi te tienes que ver el directo de
see it today. We'll see it today. Susy Rock,
Susi lo vemos hoy lo vemos hoy Susy Rock
what she said about Felipe will
lo que dijo sobre Felipe te va a
interest you. Ah, no, Luar, you're here,
interesar Ah eso no luar estás por aquí
Luar. Look, let's see what that is. We didn't
luar mira a ver qué es eso no lo
know.
sabíamos
Well, I know the topic is about Felipe.
bueno sé que el tema es lo de Felipe
But first I have to deal with other
Pero primero tengo que tratar otros
issues,
temas
okay, let's see. I wanted to deal first with the topic
vale a ver quería tratar primero el tema
of the
de la demanda de
turboplane lawsuit that I uploaded from my cell phone, no, I
turboplane que subí del móvil no que lo
literally uploaded it at the door of the
subí literalmente en la puerta de la
church. Javi, have you found out about the
iglesia Javi te has enterado de las
four lawsuits that they've filed against
cuatro demandas que le han puesto a
Sasel? I'm going to find out today that we're going
sasel me voy a enterar hoy que lo vamos
to see it. I'm going to find out today that we're going
a ver me voy a enterar hoy que lo vamos
to  to check but the other day I
a a revisar pero es que el otro día os
was commenting to you from my cell phone
estuve comentando desde el móvil
about this
sobre sobre este clip de
turboplane clip and we discussed it okay on top of that I did
turboplane y lo comentamos vale encima
a little research to
me he metido a investigar un poquito a
see who is delox's lawyer And that
ver quién es el abogado de delox Y que
must be a little bit messed up David Mena
debe em chigado un poquito David Mena
starts strong David Mena Of course
empieza fuerte David Mena Claro que sí
50 pieces of members that
50 pedazos de miembros que acaba de
David just gave away a kiss David let's see if you
regalar David un beso David a ver si me
shut my mouth let's see if you shut my
cerráis la boca a ver si me cerráis la
mouth and it will be that here tonight we reach
boca y será que aquí llegamos esta noche
at least 2000 at least
por lo menos a los 2000 por lo menos a
2000 I'm not going to tell you that we
los 2000 yo no os voy a decir que
reach 3000 like before And
lleguemos a los 3000 como antiguamente Y
such But man at least 2000
tal Pero hombre por lo menos a los 2000
so that tomorrow I go to the
para que yo mañana vaya a la
gentlemen guys they have reached 2000
señoreros chavales han llegado a 2000
members let's see
miembros a ver
turban has been
turban ha estado
investigating okay because he is a good
investigando vale porque es un buen
investigator and he has been investigating
investigador y ha estado investigando
Who is
Quién es el
delox's lawyer because it's not like the burofax already puts it to you
delox porque no es como que ya te lo
turbo plan or rather it's not like it's already in the
turbo plan o sea no es como que ya en el
burofax when they send you the burofax
burofax cuando te mandan el burofax
before the  demand it's not like I already
antes de la demanda no es como que ya te
told you what law firm
pusiera qué bufete
it was to
era
be the same lawyer that
ser el mismo abogado que que tiene el
Javi Oliveira has and I see that in his
Javi oliveira y y veo que en su foto de
Twitter profile picture he has a picture with
perfil de Twitter tiene una foto con
Frank
Frank
Cuesta Of course because it's a Twitter that he
cuesta Claro porque es un Twitter que él
uses on a personal level okay a lawyer
utiliza a nivel personal vale un abogado
just like a truck driver just like
al igual que un camionero al igual que
a fruit seller can have an account that
un frutero puede tener una cuenta que
is related to his work and another
esté relacionada con su trabajo y otra
that is related Well on a
que esté relacionada Pues a nivel
personal level no
personal no
eh
eh
with his life on YouTube and on the networks you
con su vida en YouTube y en las redes
know I mean a guy can be a certain
sabes o sea un tío puede ser de una
way on YouTube in fact I know
forma en YouTube de hecho yo conozco a
several lawyers who are a certain way on
varios abogados que son de una forma en
YouTube and in the media even but
YouTube y en los medios incluso pero
then in court he behaves
luego en el jugado se comporta de otra
differently which in the end is what
manera que al final es lo que nos
interests us okay me personally I
interesa vale a mí personalmente yo lo
've said it about David Bravo and I can't say
he dicho de David Bravo y no puedo decir
the opposite about Pablo I mean really to
lo contrario de Pablo o sea realmente a
me well I don't like Maybe some
mí pues no me Mola A lo mejor algunas
expressions or some things and such but I
expresiones o algunas cosas y tal pero
really don't care I
realmente me da igual
would prefer not to some things no and
preferiría que no algunas cosas no y que
not to get into some fights well it's that I
no entrar algunas peleas bueno es que me
really don't care what
da igual realmente a mí lo que me
matters to me is the procedure okay
importa es el procedimiento vale Ya
Then the rest I don't care a bit okay And
luego lo otro me da un poco igual vale Y
I'm fine without  comments don't be
yo vale muy bien sin comentarios no sea
I think that a picture is worth a thousand
yo creo que una imagen vale más que mil
words he's Delox's lawyer,
palabras es el abogado de delox el
Delox's lawyer and Javi Oliveira's lawyer. He's not a
abogado de delox y del Javi oliveira No
fan of Fran
es es fan de Fran
Cuesta. Well let's see if he's at his house, if he's
cuesta Bueno a ver si está en su casa si
at the sanctuary. I mean if you're seeing if you
en el santuario O sea si estás viendo si
're seeing that he's at his house and that he
estás viendo que está en su casa y que
has
tiene
the
tatuado el
Hedgehog tattooed which by the way I'll get it tattooed
Erizo que por cierto me lo tatuaré
when I go
cuando vaya
eh literally he's not a fan he'll be a
eh literalmente no es un fan será un
friend no a picture is worth a thousand
amigo no una imagen vale más que mil
words he's Delox's lawyer eh
palabras es el abogado de delox eh el
Delox's lawyer and Javi Oliveira he's not a
abogado de delox y del Javi oliveira No
fan of Fran Cuesta I don't understand
es es fan de Fran cuesta no yo entiendo
this he has a photo of him I understand that
esto tiene una foto suya entiendo que
he even appears with Frank Cuesta I think it's
sale él incluso con Frank cuesta creo
him he hasn't gone on an
que es él no se ha ido de a una
expedition to the jungle with Frank Cuesta I mean it's
expedición a la jungla con Frank cuesta
not that he's a fan of his he's a
O sea no es que sea fan suyo es que es
super
super
fan I mean it's not that he's a fan do you believe I was going to
fan O sea no es que sea fan me crea que
say It's not that he's a fan he's
iba a decir No es que sea fan es que es
his friend no no it's not that he's a fan he's a
su amigo no no no es que sea fan es
super fan because everyone knows that
superfan porque todo el mundo sabe que
you can go to Francua's house as a
tú te puedes ir a la casa de francua de
tourist whenever you want I mean you
turismo cuando te dé la gana o sea tú
take a plane you go to Thailand and since  you
coges un avión vas a Tailandia y ya que
're there so you show up at
estás por allí pues te presentas en la
francoa's house and well you can
casa de francoa Y bueno pues puedes
be there taking pictures and doing whatever the
estar allí haciéndote fotos y ha lo que
[ __ ] you want in someone else's house it
te salga de la [__] en la casa de otro
turns out that I find out that delox
no resulta que me entero que delox
also wants to sue the serl who
también quiere denunciar a la serl que
is another youtuber of criticism but I
es otro youtuber de críticas pero me
find out that he is going to sue him for
entero de que le va a denunciar por
insults no I mean it seems that the serl in
insultos no O sea se ve que la serl en
some videos or in some live streams
algunos vídeos o en algunos directos
has insulted delox they
pues le ha insultado a delox le ha
called him scum no And of course
llamado Escoria no Y claro
and scum doesn't sound like me or yes scum I don't
y Escoria no me suena a mí o sí Escoria
know the other day we were putting
no sé el otro día lo estuvimos poniendo
the tweets here that were that laser said
aquí los tweets que eran que laser decía
no no I only reacted to a
no no yo solamente reaccioné a un
live stream The only thing I did to delo
directo Yo lo único que le hice a delo
was that I reacted to a live stream where they
fue que reaccioné a un directo donde le
called him a scammer and that's it eh And the end
llamaban estafador y y ya está eh Y fin
also he said and the end okay And
además decía y fin vale Y
cool so much that he liked the
chinón tanto que le gustaba a él el
cool no and it turns out it's a lie of course
chinón no y resulta que es mentira claro
how does he not Open the postman well he doesn't know
como no le Abre al cartero pues no sabe
the content of the complaint Open the
el contenido de la demanda Ábrele al
postman And then you will know the content
cartero Y entonces sabrás el contenido
of the complaint and there they remember you Well
de la demanda y y ahí te recuerdan Pues
everyone  the tweets that are certified
todos los tweets que están certificados
where used and in videos and live
donde utado y en vídeos y directos
many and there is
muchos
one there is an extension of the
e hay hay una hay una ampliación de la
lawsuit that I do not know at what time that is done I do
demanda que no sé en qué momento se hace
not know if before or after the
eso no sé si antes o después de la
preliminary hearing I am not a jurist okay
audiencia previa no soy jurista vale
But I know that there is apart from what was put
Pero sé que hay aparte de lo que se puso
in the lawsuit I know that there is a scammer it is
en la demanda sé que hay una estafador
an accusation of a crime Let's see, these
es una acusación de delito A ver es que
lawsuits are for the right to
las demandas estas por derecho al
honor sometimes they are because you impute
honor algunas veces son porque tú imput
facts that damage the image of another
hechos que perjudican la imagen de otro
okay or they can be for insults okay for
vale o pueden ser por insultos vale por
example the issues that I have had have
ejemplo los temas que yo he tenido han
been for having
sido por por tener un
unnecessary vocabulary they consider it in
vocabulario innecesario lo consideran en
the law or I mean there are many times that there are
la ley o sea es que hay muchas veces que
people okay who play with this
hay gente vale que juega con esto de las
lawsuit thing like Win michu wanted to do
demandas como quiso hacer Win michu
wismichu wanted to do that with with the naen
wismichu quiso hacer eso con con el naen
no Win michu wanted to be like the
no Win michu quería ser como que la
lawsuit gives you the reason in the controversy
demanda te da la razón en la polémica
that you have with that person the
que tú tengas con esa persona las
lawsuits can give you the reason in
demandas puedes que te den la razón en
the controversy the
la polémica
content of the lawsuit is the controversy if
contenido de la demanda es la polmica si
the lawsuit what is judging you are
la demanda lo que te está juzgando son
the insults that does not give you the reason
los insultos eso no te da a ti la razón
to me the lawsuit none of the lawsuits
a mí la demanda ninguna de las demandas
that  I've had they prove me wrong in none
que he tenido me quitan la razón en nada
of my arguments or anything
de mis argumentos ni de nada simplemente
I simply should have saved some
me tenía que haber ahorrado algunas
expressions okay in all the lawsuits
expresiones vale en todas las demandas
okay that have been put on me in life
vale que me han puesto en la vida
and there are many people who think that Ah
y hay mucha gente que se piensa que Ah
well reason because he won the trial or
bueno razón porque ha ganado el juicio o
the other one didn't in the case of Win michu for
el otro no en el caso de Win michu por
example I wanted to do that Look look the
ejemplo quise hacer eso Mira mira el
first one the first one the first one to fall will
primero el primero el primero que cae
fall one by one no of course let's see
caerá uno por uno no Claro a ver es que
the moment there are insults they
en el momento que haya insultos te
condemn you unless the other has
condenan a no ser que el otro te haya
said insults to you At the same level and it's
dicho a ti insultos Al mismo nivel y sea
a fight in which you are more or less At the
una pelea en el que esté más o menos Al
same level But you violate the honor of
mismo nivel Pero tú vulner el honor de
a person at the moment there is an
una persona en el momento que hay un
insult okay For example I say the
insulto vale Yo por ejemplo lo digo las
lawsuits that I have filed that this these
demandas que yo he puesto que este estos
last two or three months I have filed two one
últimos dos o tres meses he puesto dos
to a youtuber of the heart youtuber
una a un youtuber del corazón youtuber
journalist I don't know what it is
periodista No sé lo que es
exactly but well I have
exactamente pero bueno yo se la he
filed it as a youtuber for his for his for the
puesto como youtuber por su por los
insults that he has made to me are for
insultos que me ha hecho son por
insults
insultos
now then I can debate with him on
ahora ya luego yo puedo debatir con él
other topics but they are insults okay to
otros temas pero son los insultos vale a
a lady also a youtuber who  I filed
una señora también youtuber que le puse
a lawsuit this last month, well, there you
una demanda a este último mes bueno Ahí
go, a little bit of everything, insults, accusations
va un poco de todo insultos imputaciones
of crimes and so on,
de delitos y demás
okay, without further ado, so in the case of lerl it
vale sin más entonces en el caso de lerl
is no longer just the issue of
ya no es solamente el tema de que lo
accusing him of fraud, which we will get to
acuse estafa que ahora iremos a eso más
later, okay, Roman. Thank you very much, if not,
adelante vale Román Muchas gracias si no
in the case of lasl he would already be a party,
es que en el caso de lasl ya fuera parte
although he could justify it, it's not that
aunque él pudiera justificar no es que
I consider that this is a scam, what he
yo Considero que esto es una estafa lo
did, I don't know what, it doesn't matter,
que la ha hecho no sé qué da igual sería
the insults he made would be completely unnecessary, I
completamente innecesario los insultos
understand.
hace me entiend
So go, no,
Entonces ve
speculate here, join together because it would be
nooner especular aquí ainar unado porque
guessing the future and in
sería adivinar el futuro y en los
trials you never know, but man, it's
juicios nunca se saben pero hombre la lo
very complicated,
tiene muy complicado
okay, very complicated that they don't condemn him and
vale muy complicado que no lo condenen y
he
él lo
knows it. That's why he doesn't open the
sabe Por eso no abre
mailman because of these insults, I mean, the
cartero por estos insultos o sea el
lawyer who is a fan of Frank, it's hard to
abogado que es fan de Frank cuesta
report him to
denunciar a
his work, I mean, if a client comes to him
ha su trabajo o sea si le viene un
and says, I want you to sue
cliente y dice quiero que demandes a
this guy, or hey, this is sueable, the lawyer is
este o Oye esto es demandable el abogado
doing his job, the lawyer is not going to
hace su trabajo el abogado no va a
sue the serl or you, or delox, okay,
demandar a la serl ni a ti a delox vale
but nevertheless, he is a fan of Fran, it's
pero sin embargo es es fan de Fran
hard that every day on Twitter he
cuesta que todos los días en Twitter
calls  scum to 25
Llama scoria a 25 personas
different people This is the [ __ ] level I
diferentes Este es el puñetero nivel te
swear This is the level
lo juro Este es el nivel
of So the logic of turb plan is that
de O sea la lógica de turb plan es que
the lawyer is a friend of Fran cua And how is
el abogado es amigo de Fran cua Y cómo
the lawyer going to put a kiss megadron or in other words
el abogado va a poner un beso megadron o
the lawyer is a friend of Fran costs
sea el abogado es amigo de Fran cuesta
therefore a client of that
por lo tanto un cliente de ese
lawyer cannot sue someone who
abogado no puede demandar a alguien que
insults him because francoa
lo insulte porque francoa
insults I really am
insulta yo de verdad
I am or rather the conclusions that they
son yo son o sea las conclusiones a la
reach eh It
que llegan eh
was you him at home thinking I'm going to
Fu tú él en su casa pensando voy a
investigate the investigation go into the
investigar la investigación meterse en
lawyer's Twitter and see that he has
el Twitter del abogado y ver que tiene
a banner and says Ah francua insults How
un banner y dice Ah francua insulta Cómo
is it that this lawyer is going to go and
es que este abogado va a [__] y va a
file a lawsuit for insults it's like
poner una demanda por insultos es como
man I know I mean I think it's not even necessary
tío yo sé o sea creo que no hace falta
but those are I mean Turbo
ni que pero esos son o sea es que Turbo
plan is literally like these haters
plan es literalmente como los hater
of him the nauter flay this the Rich the
estos de el el nauter flay este el Rich
critic there
el crítico
are a lot of these
el Hay un montón de cuentas de estas de
Twitter accounts he thinks the same as them the
Twitter él piensa igual que ellas lo
bad thing is that he has more
malo es que él tiene más
followers I understand Well the bad or the
seguidores me enti Bueno lo malo o lo
good I don't care I don't know well for him
bueno Me da igual No sé bien para él
but
pero
eh he thinks the same eh I mean he arrives  to the
eh piensa igual eh o sea llega a las
same
mismas
conclusions comes to the same
conclusiones llega a las mismas
conclusions in the same way eh I mean well that's it well
conclusiones de la misma forma eh o sea
how is that
pues ya está pues cómo va a [__] ese
lawyer going to take any lawsuit from
abog y va a [__] ninguna demanda ya de
any client when he has a friend who
ningún cliente cuando tiene un amigo que
insults it's like Well then whoever
insulta es como Bueno pues quien se
feels insulted by Francua should sue
sienta insultado por francua que demande
Francua the lawyer I mean if they call
francua del abogado O sea si llaman
one of her clients scum on the internet
Escoria por internet a un cliente suyo
no but the cane tillero is not a hater
no pero el cane tillero no es un hater
Sari you're making me the cane tillero
Sari me estás poniendo el cane tillero
the cane tillero I think it's very obvious
el cane tillero Yo creo que es muy Obvio
who he is And now and I'll tell you the
Quién es Y ya y ya os contaré los
details that the
detalles que se está preparando el
ground is being prepared because he knows that
terreno porque sabe que ya mismo se va a
the matter is going to be known soon No but if Fran
saber el tema No pero si lo hace Fran
Cuesta does it it's very good I'm a fan of his and I'm
cuesta está muy bien soy fan suyo y me
going to the sanctuary with him to visit
voy al santuario con él a visitar
animals J well no if Francua does it It
animales J bueno no si lo hace francua
's very good in Med to the sanctuary no we don't
Está muy bien en Med al santuario no no
know maybe Pablo doesn't like
sabemos a lo mejor a Pablo no le parecen
Francua's insults Or yes I don't
bien los insultos de francua O sí no lo
know this is a
sé esto es un
video a bit of everything no So how did we
vídeo un poco todo no Entonces como nos
go too far I mean This is a video of I don't know
pasamos o sea Este es un vídeo de no sé
if you remember these people they are the ones with the
si os acordáis de esta gente son los de
fixed term mortgages  These are two
las hipotecas a plazos fijo son dos
people who even made it to
personas que llegaron Ahí incluso a
Sálvame Delux because they appeared in a
sálvame delux porque salieron en un
video in which, well, I don't know if
vídeo en el que bueno Yo no sé si lo
they confirmed it or
confirmaron ellos o
not, it went viral. This video of them is
no se hizo viral Este vídeo de ellos
worth it in which they appeared a little, well,
vale en el que salían un poco bueno
[Music]
[Música]
rare, as well as an expert in
raros así como experto en inversiones
financial investments, real estate investments, and a
financieras inversiones inmobiliarias y
European financial advisor.
asesor financiero europeo
Silvia. Hello, I'm Silvia Charro, a consultant
Silvia Hola soy Silvia Charro consultora
at Engel and Walkers. My specialty is
de Engel and walkers mi especialidad es
real estate investments and a
en inversiones inmobiliarias y asesora
mortgage advisor. We believe that this is a
en hipotecas consideramos que este es un
time when it's worth talking about
momento en el cual merece la pena hablar
real estate, it's worth talking about
de inmueble merece la pena hablar de
housing, investment in housing, and
vivienda de inversión en vivienda y de
well, this video went viral, I don't know
Bueno Este vídeo se hizo viral no sé por
why, okay. I don't know what time I recorded it, it's
qué vale No sé a qué hora lo grabaría
not worth it, but for many of these
tampoco vale pero para muchos de esta
people, for many of the haters, these
gente para muchos de los hater esta
people who fight each other, apparently have
gente que se pegan por lo visto tienen
a problem with him, they call him a scammer,
un problema con lo llaman estafador
too, and so on. He's not the
también y demás no es la
source, okay, for many of the people, this one with
Fuente vale para mucho de la gente esta
the accounts, these, and so on, these
de los de las cuentas estas y demás esta
people are sources. It's not the main
gente es fuente No es la principal
source, eh, apparently, the main
fuente eh por lo visto la principal
source for calling Delox a scammer is
fuente para llamar a delox estafador es
some videos from someone who, in addition,
unos vídeos de alguien que además
eh, makes things up, twit, so what I'm talking about.
eh se inventa twit o sea por lo que me
was saying delox in the in the
estuvo diciendo delox en los en los
videos themselves takes twist Maybe from
propios vídeos saca twist A lo mejor de
Dallas that don't exist does them with
Dallas que no existen los hace con el
Photoshop okay Well apparently
Photoshop vale Bueno pues por lo visto
these people have had something of a trial
esta gente han tenido algo de un juicio
Wait until we see it and
Espérate que lo veamos y os
we tell you cetea a little bit of everything no
comentamos cetea un poco todo no
then and as we went quite a bit with
entonces e como nos pasamos bastante con
Santi we had the doubt that death
Santi teníamos la duda que la muerte
Even live but very ugly I mean we
Incluso en directo pero muy feo o sea
messed with his whole family it was something
nos metimos con toda su familia fue algo
and that Therefore I also show it because I
y que Por ende además lo enseño porque
have jurisprudence for those things and it
tengo jurisprudencia para esas cosas y
is that if with Santi We had a great time
es que si con Santi Nos pasamos un huevo
and nothing has happened to me So
y a mí no me ha pasado nada nos Entonces
I think that if I to this gentleman who
yo pienso que si yo a este señor que lo
put it back and a half I [ __ ] all
puesto de vuelta y media me cago todos
his dead in his alive in well you don't
sus muertos en sus vivos en bueno no lo
know in his children in horrible or rather in
sabéis en sus hijos en horrible o sea de
a way that I don't recognize myself okay I have
un modo en el que no me reconozco vale
gone very ugly with this gentleman and
me he puesto muy fea con este señor y no
nothing has happened to me open your eyes a
me ha pasado nada abrid los ojos un
little If there are only people scamming on
poquito Si solo hay gente estafando por
YouTube and nobody can see giving their opinion
YouTube y no pueda ha ver nadie opinando
objectively because I know about economics
con objetividad porque yo s de economía
and financial products what is
y s de productos financieros qué nos
left then only that it is It is  that
queda entonces solo que está Es que de
these super financial advisors
verdad estos super asesores financieros
are really so short that they have not even
son tan cortitos que ni siquiera se han
read the sentence of which they are
leído la sentencia de la cual están
bragging and showing themselves so
sacando pecho y mostrándose tan
proud here clearly in the own
orgullosos aquí claramente en el propio
text that they show in their live it is
texto que ellos muestran en su directo
seen why they were brought to
se ve por qué motivo fueron llevados
justice and it is for having accused
ante la justicia y es por haber acusado
a person of committing a fraud a
a una persona de cometer una estafa una
person from a company but
persona de una empresa Pero por ningún
nowhere is it mentioned in the written complaint or
lado se menciona en el escrito demanda o
in the sentence about the accusations
en la sentencia sobre los señalamientos
of wishing death meddling with the
de desear la muerte el meterse con la
family and children of this person of
familia y los hijos de esta persona de
which they also feel
lo cual ellos también se sienten
proud and they say is that nothing happened to me
orgullosos y dicen es que no me pasado
as we can see here very clearly it
nada como podemos ver aquí muy clarito
says read the written complaint in its
dice leído el escrito de demanda en su
entirety there are no more
integridad no se observan en él más
statements or imputations attributed to
afirmaciones o imputaciones atribuidas a
the defendants than those previously
los demandados que las anteriormente
cited the object of the
citadas debiendo quedar el objeto del
process and the controversy should be
proceso y de la la controversia
limited to them in attention to the
limitadas a ellas en atención a la
unanimous and reiterated jurisprudence that
unánime y reiterada jurisprudencia que
understands that it is in the written complaint
entiende que es en el escrito de demanda
in which the facts
en el que sean de introducir los hechos
that support the plaintiff's claim are to be introduced without
que fundamentan la pretensión actora sin
these being able to be introduced
que estos se puedan introducir con
later, that is to say that simply
posterioridad es decir que simplemente
this process was limited to  the
este proceso se limitó a los
accusations of fraud, nothing more about the
señalamientos de estafa no más sobre lo
other thing, no, it's not like nothing happened to them
otro no no es que no les haya pasado
and you can say whatever
nada y que tú puedas decir las
nonsense you want about a
barbaridades que quieras sobre una
person and get away with it, no, what's true is that
persona y salir indemne no lo que lo que
this is like the thing, yes, well what
sí esto como la
happens is that the lawyer for
lo Sí bueno pasa es que el abogado de
this company and this man didn't make
esta empresa y este señor a ellos no les
the other accusations or the
clavó los otros señalamientos ni los
other statements and that's why they got off
otros dichos y por eso es que salieron
scot-free, but the
entre comillas impunes pero es que de
truth is that these people are too obtuse and
verdad esta gente es demasiado obtusa y
give very bad advice, it's terrible, I mean,
da consejos muy malos es terrible o sea
terrible, I mean, they had a lawsuit, they had
terrible o sea tuvieron una tuvieron una
a
sea tuvieron una han tenido una
lawsuit, the Arona court of first instance.
demanda jugado de primera instancia de
Well, I'll touch on that one, I think it doesn't command
Bueno ese tocaré creo no manda en
protection of the right to honor. Because you
protección derecho al honor Porque tú
insult in your videos and I say, well,
insultas en tus vídeos y digo Bueno pues
what do you want me to say? He's not
pues qué quieres que te diga no es un
stupid, it's just that you see, it's Let's see, there are
estúpido es que ya ves es A ver es que
people, there are people who are a little bit, it's a
hay gente hay gente que es un poco es un
little bit stupid. One thing is to insult, you know,
poco tonra una cosa es insultar sabes
then insulting can be fat, ugly,
entonces insultar puede ser gordo feo
idiot, disgusting, but another thing is
idiota asqueroso pero otra cosa es
calling someone a scammer, that's
Llamar estafador a alguien que eso es
something else, that's not an insult, that's a
otra cosa que eso no es un insulto eso
crime, you
le estás le estás aplicando un delito tú
're saying that they have a crime, I don't know.
estás diciendo que tiene un delito no sé
what's that [ __ ] called but if I if I
cóm se llama esa [__] pero si yo si yo
say that you went out yesterday and
digo que sal que tú ayer saliste y y te
slept with two 17 year old girls I'm
tiraste a dos chavalas de 17 años estoy
charging you with a crime in some way of
imputando un delito de alguna manera de
14 or 12 or whatever so it's
14 o de 12 o lo que sea entonces es que
not the same as saying you're a scoundrel dude I
no es lo mismo decir eres un golfo tío O
mean it's not the same look at the problem
sea no es lo mismo mira el problema que
with these people who have channels
hay con esta gente que tienen canales
that are dedicated to that they only dedicate themselves to
que se dedican a eso solo se dedican a
criticizing they dedicate themselves to four people
criticar se dedican a a cuatro personas
effectively yes Yes also they are
efectivamente sí Sí además están
obsessed with Dallas with Javi and
obsesionados con Dallas con Javi y con
four
cuatro
more but I the thing about the obsession dude I do
más pero yo el tema de la obsesión tío
n't even watch it anymore I mean because let's
Yo es que ya no lo veo ni o sea porque
see you can do the thing about the ler
vamos a ver tú puedes lo del tema ler
len issue and And these channels are
len y Y estos canales
no longer personal dude it's personal and
no ya es personal tío ya es personal y
to the point of selling their opinion and changing
al punto de vender su opinión y cambiar
their opinion for example talking to
su opinión por ejemplo hablarse con
the talk to
la hablarse con la madre de la
Miare's mother How was it that they sent me
miare Cómo fue lo que me mandaron
dude how was it that they sent me I mean
tío cómo fue lo que me mandaron o sea
because you say Well it's not that I
porque tú dices Bueno no es que yo me
really dislike Dallas and I can't watch it I can't
cae muy mal Dalas y no lo puedo ver no
stand it whatever it is okay well
lo soporto lo que sea vale bueno
perfect in the end each one has  your
perfecto al final cada uno tiene su su
opinion and you might like one better, another
opinión y te puede caer uno mejor otro
worse or
peor o lo que
whatever but this
sea pero ya esto
dude wait and see if I
tío espérate a ver si lo
can find it level defend this
encuentro nivel defender esto
dude according to the panis Argos Argos Argos
tío según los panis Argos Argos Argos
Argos I mean level
Argos o sea nivel
defend that the dog that these
defender que el perro que tienen esa
people have is not
gente no es
Argos level
Argos nivel
now a kiss
ya un beso
David It's that they sent me some screenshots
David Es que me mandaron unas capturas
today
hoy
this
esto
dude, I mean these
tío o sea estas
jokes well it's going in the right direction You have to suck up to me
bromas bueno va por bien camino Tienes
and let me
que hacerme la pelota y dejar que te
write the scripts for the
haga los guiones de los
videos it's true the script for the video
vídeos es verdad el guión del vídeo
shut your mouth Javi you and
cierra la boca Javi lo hiciste tú y
David Bravo made it I mean these are things since you
David Bravo o sea son cosas ya que tú
say Well I don't like Dallas okay I
dices Bueno me cae mal el Dallas vale lo
criticize him or because he gives you visitors okay you
critico o porque te da visita vale tú
say Well it's that this topic gives me
dices Bueno es que este tema me da
visitors Okay here we've had the
visita Okay aquí hemos tenido el tema de
Johnny dep topic we've had the
Johnny dep hemos tenido el tema de la
Roso Carrasco topic we've had a lot of
roso Carrasco hemos tenido un montón de
topics tobia a kiss that when it's the
temas tobía un beso que cuando es el
moment well you have to exploit it
momento pues tú lo tienes que explotar
the gossip channels have to
los canales de salseo tienen que
exploit the topics I mean when it's
explotar los temas o sea cuando es el
Gref and Willy's topic Well
tema de gref y Willy Bueno pues nosotros
here we do a live show then we release
aquí hacemos un directo luego sacamos
800 shorts or we release the extracts later
800 short o sacamos los extractos luego
too  maybe there's a video on the
también a lo mejor hay un vídeo en el
main channel edit or whatever but
canal principal edita o lo que sea pero
they're only Dallas channels man And
son canales únicamente de Dallas tío Y
if there's no Dallas I'm going to the debate that he
si no hay Dallas me voy a el debate que
did with j
ha hecho con j
redhead I mean they're things since
pelirrojo o sea son cosas ya que
[Music] are
[Música]
not things since they go like beyond you
no son cosas ya que van como más allá
know I mean everything is
sabes o sea todo es
Dallas
Dallas
Dallas is worth literally
Dallas vale literal
man all
tío todo
Dallas because it has to please that
Dallas porque tiene que complacer a a a
audience I mean do you understand Because there are
a ese público O sea me entiendes Porque
also channels that don't like
hay canales también a los que no les cae
Dallas and they criticize it but they're
bien el Dallas y le critican pero van
doing all the topics there is I mean
haciendo todos los temas que haya O sea
imagine they talk about ibay they talk about this
imagínate hablan de ibay hablan de esto
tomorrow this and when it's Dallas's turn they give
mañana esto y cuando le toca al Dallas
Dallas a hard time because they can't
le dan caña al Dallas porque no lo
stand it but every day it's
soportan pero que todos los días sea
Dallas And if Dallas isn't on these
Dallas Y si Dallas no está estas
vacations I'm out now it's weird I mean it's
vacaciones me saco ya es Es raro o sea
like taking something personally as
es como tomarte algo a lo personal como
if you had done something to yourself you
si a ti te hubieras hecho algo
know I don't understand it at the level that
sabes no lo entiendo a nivel de que
now they're going to sue you and the problem they have is
ahora te van a denunciar e el problema
that until now it has been
que tienen es que hasta ahora les ha
free for them because people said oh it
salido gratis porque la gente decía va
's YouTube and that's it no and people didn't
es YouTube y y ya está no y la gente no
sue And such But [ __ ] now that
demandaba Y tal Pero [__] ahora que
the lawsuits start to fall now they say
empiezan a caer las demandas ahora dicen
[ __ ] but this is always how it's been done What's
[__] pero si esto siempre se hizo así
going on No why not now already already
Qué pasa No por qué ahora no ya ya pues
because because there comes a time when they
porque porque llega un momento en que te
tell you Look, there are things that you can't
dicen Mira pues hay cosas que no tú
give your opinion about a person
puedes dar tu opinión sobre una persona
you can be but the insult well well no there is no there is no
tú puedes estar pero el insulto pues
right to
pues pues no no hay no hay un derecho al
insult in Spanish legislation that
insulto en la legislación española ese
's the problem of
es el problema
course you can't
claro no puedes
insult because len says said in a
insultar porque dice el len decía en un
tweet Well now we'll see later I
tweet Bueno ahora luego lo veremos que
asked him here to al luare to
pedía le pedía aquí a al luare que me
make me a small compilation to
hiciera un un pequeño recopilatorio para
catch up and he put some
ponerme al día y me puso aquí algunos
clicks here that are quite funny
clic que son bastante divertidos
Look, I have to do this one day
Mira esto lo tengo que hacer yo un día
eh I have to do it one day with more
eh lo tengo que hacer un día con más
clicks that I have saved somewhere eh not
click que tengo por ahí guardado eh
even you were such a hater But look,
ni tú eras tan hater Pero mira es que lo
mine is
mío es
different, man, mine is different
diferente vieje lo mío es diferente
because first I did have something
porque lo primero yo sí tenía algo
personal against Dallas because
personal contra el Dallas porque el
Dallas answered me I would fight with
Dallas me contestaba yo me peleaba con
him we got into a fight we both had a
él nos enganchamos los dos hacíamos
debate he insulted me too
debate él me me insultó también el
Dallas I mean Dallas messed with me we
Dallas o sea el Dallas se metió conmigo
fought I mean there was and besides I was
nos peleamos o sea hubo y aparte a mí me
doing well what do you want no you say
iba bien que quieres que no tú dices
Well then he sues you  You can
Bueno pues te demanda tú puedes hacer
face your lawyer you can face
frente a tu abogado puedes hacer frente
your things okay but these people
a tus cosas vale pero es que esta gente
literally what can they earn that they
literalmente qué pueden ganar que hayan
had a good month that they earned
tenido un mes bueno que hayan ganado
500 or in other words it's completely ruining their life
500 o sea es arruinarse la vida por
that they won't even have, let's
completo que no tendrán ni siquiera
go I don't know what they have Maybe they
vamos No lo sé lo que tienen A lo mejor
work in a very good place but from what I
trabajan en un sitio muy bueno pero por
understand they don't have a
lo que yo tengo entendidos no tiene un
very good job and the numbers are you
trabajo muy bueno y los números son
know what I'm telling you I mean the numbers
sabes lo que te digo o sea los números
are what they
son los que
are I criticized Dallas but you always
son criticaba a Dallas pero siempre
commented on other topics but apart from that I did
comentabas otros temas pero aparte es
n't comment on other topics but apart from that it was
que no comentaba otros temas pero aparte
another time there was another image about
era otra época había otra imagen sobre
Dallas I believed the other side that was what
Dallas me creía la otra parte que era lo
motivated me the most that I believed that I was
que más me motivaba que me creía que era
a person who was having a bad time
una person que lo estaba pasando mal
okay but apart from that it was going
vale pero aparte a mí me iba
well for me I mean but getting into these things
bien o sea pero meterte en estos rollos
for what
pa para lo que
you have I don't know if I don't know if you understand me
tienes no sé si me no sé si me entendéis
okay there are people who have goals that
vale ha gente que tiene objetivos que
are good And now I'm come on I've seen a
son bueno Y ahora yo vamos he visto un
few of these clips that have caught me in the
poco estos clips que me ha cogido el el
place and I'm doing somersaults I mean I have to
lugar y yo estoy dando volteretas o sea
make one well I have to make
tengo que hacer uno bien tengo que hacer
a good video Maybe for the
un vídeo bien A lo mejor para el canal
main channel it's that I don't want to make a
principal es que no le quiero hacer
video  to this kid because probably
vídeo a este chaval porque probablemente
one day too, I mean, I'm
algún día también o sea yo estoy
also pending on timing some
pendiente también de minutar unas
things okay But oh well, it's not a
cosillas vale Pero bueno tampoco pasa
problem you can keep commenting
nada tú puedes seguir comentando
as long as the same
mientras que yo no caigan los mismos
insults that have fallen on me don't fall It's not a
insultos que la ha caído conmigo No pasa
problem but I'm doing somersaults with
nada pero estoy dando volteretas con
this lawsuit because of course now I
esta demanda porque claro yo ahora
remember things that I have saved
recuerdo cosas que yo tengo guardadas
about him sweet a kiss click that I
sobre él dulce un beso click que yo
have saved
tengo guardado
about, I mean, I've heard him
sobre o sea yo lo he escuchado a él
say things about my
decir cosas de mis procedimientos
judicial procedures as if they were Well, I mean
judiciales como si fueran Bueno o sea
as if they were crimes you know and it's like
como si fueran crímenes sabes y es como
now now that they've sued him
ahora ahora que lo han demandado a él
now he's giving them notice you know look
ahora está su avisando sabes mira
listen maybe media-related maybe to
escucha a lo mejor mediáticos a lo mejor
use it okay people who have
para utilizarlo vale gente que tiene
objectives that are maybe media-related
objetivos que son a lo mejor mediáticos
maybe to use it as some
a lo mejor para utilizarlo como algún
kind of argument public this It's me
tipo de argumento pública esto Soy yo
talking to delos okay here he's
hablando con delos vale aquí está
thinking about Rocío Carrasco for
pensando lo de Rocío Carrasco por
example there aren't many people who file
ejemplo no hay mucha gente que pone
lawsuits eh For example wismichu
demandas eh Por ejemplo wismichu la
wismichu's lawsuit against nauter
demanda de wismichu a nauter
and I'm sorry but it's like that and I know them I've been
y Lo siento pero es así y los conozco Ya
with them for many years and I
llevo muchos años con ellos y los
know their movements perfectly
conozco sus movimientos perfectamente
the lawsuits of the lawsuit of  wismichu
las demandas de la demanda de wismichu
auter is to make a headline okay it's
auter es para sacar un titular vale es
to make a headline that says what
para sacar un titular que diga lo que
happens is that it didn't go well for him but
pasa es que no le salió bien pero la
wim's lawsuit was to make a headline
demanda de wim era para sacar un titular
that said a youtuber who
que dijera condenado un youtuber que
said that Win michu couldn't go to
dijo que Win michu no se podía ir a
Andorra because he had a
andorra porque tenía antecedentes
criminal record was convicted that was the objective of that
penales ese era el objetivo de esa
lawsuit and it was seen very clearly in the
demanda y se vio clarísimamente en la
sentence and in the trial okay and I have
sentencia y en el juicio vale y tengo
videos explaining that trial
vídeos explicando ese juicio
perfectly and and that was how it was I mean
perfectamente y y eso fue así O sea se
the lawyer was sent to get because as I
mandó al abogado a [__] porque como os
explained before a lawsuit like this
he explicado antes una demanda de estas
can be for insults or I mean
puede ser por por insulto o sea
literally they can
literalmente la pueden te la pueden
win it for insults and it has been seen already no
ganar por insultos y se ha visto ya no
and and and it does not mean that what you
y y y no quiere decir que lo que tú
are saying about the other person is a
estés diciendo de la otra persona sea
lie you know or I mean it could be because you
mentira sabes o sea puede ser porque tú
are accusing them of a false fact for
le estés imputando un hecho falso por
example in the case of the lawsuit by
ejemplo en el caso de la demanda de
delos aler to the
delos aler al al
turboplane [ __ ] crimes Okay then he
turboplane putado delitos Vale entonces
is violating his honor they can be for
está vulnerando su honor pueden ser por
other types of accusations and they do not have to
otro tipo de imputaciones e no tienen
be a crime you can
por qué ser en delito tú me puedes
accuse me of that I
acusar a mí de que yo
eh what do I tell you to you that  I know
eh qué te digo yo a ti yo que sé
something bad Okay
alguna cosa fea Bueno
[Music]
[Música]
one It's that I don't want to give any clue but one
una Es que no quiero dar pista pero una
of the things that I put in one of the
de las cosas que yo pongo en una de las
lawsuits that I've filed this month is
demandas que he puesto este mes es
because they accuse me Of having taken advantage of
porque me imputan El haberme aprovechado
a person with a mental problem okay
una persona con un problema mental vale
But well there could be several several
Pero bueno puede haber varias varias
things no And insults are one of them
cosas no Y los insultos son uno de ellos
and Win michu what he did was send the
y el Win michu lo que hizo fue mandar al
lawyer to go to the Nauter Channel to
abogado a que fuera al Canal de nauter a
insult him for 2 years he had to swallow
insul tios de 2 años se tuvo que tragar
the lawyer two years of video on nter
al abogado dos años de vídeo en nter
Play to get here the word
Play para [__] aquí la palabra
bastard here the word fool here the
cabronazo aquí la palabra tonto aquí la
word I don't know what of course I have put 20
palabra no sé qué claro le he metido 20
videos with insults You think that
vídeos con insul tios Tú te crees que
wismichu felt his honor violated
wismichu se sintió su honor vulnerado
by those insults No not at all if he
por esos insul tios No para nada si lo
says so okay What's the issue man well the
dice vale Cuál es el tema hombre pues el
issue
tema
is the issue is that he knew that he
es el tema es que sabía que por ahí
could win And if he was lucky and they
podía ganar Y si tenía suerte y le
included the video where he says about Andorra he would
metían el vídeo donde dice lo de andorra
use it for his friends the
lo utilizaba ya para sus amigos los
newspapers okay by the way since he
periódicos vale que por cierto ya que le
likes it so much now the newspapers and his
gusta tanto ya a los periódicos y a la
mother of well  to Win michu's mother-in-law,
madre de bueno a la suegra de Win michu
no, she's talking to all these
no que está hablándose con todos los
channels and all the
canales estos y con todas las cuentas de
Twitter accounts talking about my trial, how I
Twitter hablando de mi juicio de cómo yo
had my hands, what the prosecutor said,
tenía las manos de lo que dijo el fiscal
whatever, since the mother is
de lo que o sea ya que está la madre
talking to all these channels, damn, let's
hablando con todos estos canales [__] a
see if one day she talks to all these
ver si habla un día con todos estos
channels and also tells them about
canales y les cuenta también los juicios
Win michu's trials, because we have a very
de Win michu que este me tenemos uno muy
important one and no, I haven't seen any channel
importante y no no he visto ningún canal
that tells it or tweets it and many
que lo cuente ni que lo twitee y muchas
more things that, well, I'm not going to
cosas más que bueno yo no las voy a
tell because some of them are not mine, a
contar porque algunas no son mías un
kiss, Tricia, a kiss How are we, the [ __ ] is that
beso tricia un beso Cómo estamos [__] es
How things are, man How
que Cómo son las cosas tío Cómo son las
things are, no, I haven't seen yet, no
cosas que no que no he visto yo todavía
one about the news of the trial that's
que nadie de la noticia del juicio que
in a few days No, no,
hay dentro de unos días Eso no eso no
but then we go to the newspapers to
pero después vamos a los periódicos a a
announce the lawsuits, as soon as they
anunciar las demandas nada más que las
file them, just because I file them.
ponen Solamente porque las pongo
No, no, it's not that my trial, my trial,
No no es que el juicio mío el juicio mío
all these little channels that
todos los canales estos chiquinino que
are against me, I don't know how much, but not
están en contra mía no sé cuánto pero no
all the channels that have sent me a
todos los canales que me han mandado
screenshot where a literal Random contacts
captura donde un Random literal contacta
the lady, the lady tells her the
con la señora la señora le cuenta la
date, the time of the trial  you know and I've already
fecha la hora del juicio sabes y ya he
seen people out there
visto yo por ahí a gente de estas de las
who are against me giving details
que están en contra mía dando detalles
of what was discussed in
de lo que se habló en
court you
juicio
know giving details like why don't you
sabes dando detalles como por qué no
say for example that in court
contáis por ejemplo que en el juicio
you said that you never went to the
dijiste que ustedes no fuisteis a la
press to talk about me that it was me or
prensa hablar de mí nunca que fui yo o
rather literally they said that they at the trial
sea literal dijeron que ellas al juicio
she that they have never gone to the press to
ella que ellas a la prensa no han ido
talk about me and to talk about dala
nunca hablar de mí y hablar de dala
either they have never talked about dala that
tampoco nunca han hablado de dala que
must have been me I swear they said it
eso habré sido yo te lo juro lo dijeron
like that but damn then there are trials that are
así pero [__] que luego hay juicios que
not known and procedures that are not
no se conocen y procedimientos que no se
discussed But well when it arrives in
hablan Pero bueno cuando llegue dentro
a month or so I will
un mes o por ahí os lo
tell you properly that is
contaré amente eso es
instrumentalization of justice that
instrumentalización de la justicia eso
cannot be done no no I mean you have to
no se puede no no O sea tú tienes que
use justice for the
que que utilizar la justicia para los
well instrumentalization of justice I do
bueno instrumentalización de la justicia
n't know if it would be considered okay to
no sé yo si se consideraría vale
use it for a purpose that you want to
utilizarlo con un fin de que tú quieras
put a headline Well I don't know I think it would
poner un titular Pues no lo sé yo creo
n't be instrumentalization I think
que no sería instrumentalización creo
that is something else but well the purpose is
que eso es otra cosa pero bueno fin es
that justice has to be used
que se tiene que utilizar la la justicia
you can't do it for
tú no puedes hacerlo con fines
media purposes clip Ah thanks
mediáticos clip Ah gracias
lerl literally I have clips I don't  I'm going to
lerl literalmente tengo clips no lo voy
put it here now but I have it okay
a poner aquí ahora pero lo tengo vale
where to read it he says that he thinks it's
donde ler l dice que a él le parece
great that they go to the to the
fenomenal que vayan al al a la
press and that they go announce all the
prensa y que vayan anunciar todas las
lawsuits that they put to the press that he
demandas que ponen a la prensa que le
thinks it's great because since we
parece fenomenal porque como nosotros
have the YouTube channels, well, they
tenemos los canales de YouTube pues
go to the press and now it does
ellas que vayan a la prensa y ahora ya
n't seem right to him
no le está parecido
also that they go to the interview to everyone, everyone,
también que vayan al interview a todos a
everyone to the faa, the faca is like a
todos a todos al faa el faca es o sea un
consumer association where you take and announce
consumidor donde tú cojas y anuncien
all the lawsuits of these people,
todas las demandas de esta gente
that's what's freaking out
eso qué para flipar
eh David Bravo talking on television and
eh David Bravo hablando en televisión y
saying that any
diciendo lo de que cualquier persona
normal person knows that you can't give 96
normal sabe que no puedes darle 96
insults to someone, Miare's lawyer,
insultos a alguien a el abogado de miare
the bastard pulls it out, eh, the
se la saca el cabrón eh se la saca el
bastard pulls it out eh I
cabrón eh Me
love it, I think it's not going to say what I
encanta me parece yo no voy a decir lo
think but let's eh Well, let's see,
que pienso pero vamos eh Bueno a ver me
the lawyer seems peculiar to me, I'm not going to
parece peculiar el abogado a mí no voy a
say what I really think but he
decir lo que pienso realmente pero me
seems peculiar to me, I think it's peculiar but it's that
parece peculiar me parece peculiar pero
literally viar lelen that I don't know
es que literal viar lelen que no sé
who sent me the cli I have to
quién me mandó el cli lo tengo que
recover but I saw this same guy eh
recuperar pero vi a este mismo tipo eh
in a live  live where he was
en un directo en el directo donde estaba
explaining the lawsuit that has been filed against
explicando la demanda que le han puesto
him let's see when he opens the postman
a él que a ver cuando le Abre al cartero
saying criticizing Pablo Franco
diciendo criticando a Pablo Franco
because Pablo Franco argued with him
porque Pablo Franco se discutió con él
on Twitter and him and this guy started
en Twitter y el y el chico este se puso
saying in a live the other day
a decir en un directo el otro día
literally eh I have the clip of this I have to
literal eh tengo el clip de esto tengo
make a I have to make a video of
que hacer un tengo que hacer un vídeo de
all these clips but well one after the
todos estos clip pero bien uno tras
other okay
otros vale
and saying man if my lawyer
e diciendo hombre es que si mi abogado
goes on Twitter to fight with the
se pone en Twitter a pelearse con los
opponents I will fire him
contrarios lo despido
immediately I swear he said that
inmediatamente Te lo juro que dijo eso
the other day I don't know who sent me the
el otro día no sé quién me mandó el
click If someone has it
click Si alguien lo tiene que me lo
send it to me now but he started saying he started
mande ya pero se puso a decir se puso a
saying this I'm talking to you Well I don't know
decir esto te estoy hablando Pues no sé
if it was the day they sent it to me I was
si fue el día me lo mandaron estaba yo
in Asturias I don't know if it was the 29th or the
en asturia no sé si fue el día 29 o el
30th around there he did a live talking
30 por ahí hizo un directo hablando otra
again about the lawsuit that has been filed against him and
vez de la demanda que le han puesto y
that the postman won't open the door and he started
que no le abre el cartero y se puso a
saying that he thought it was a disgrace
decir que él le parecía una vergüenza
that Pablo Franco started fighting
que Pablo Franco se pusiera a pelearse
with the opponents that if he
con los con los contrarios que si él
had a lawyer that does that on
tuviera un abogado que hace eso en
Twitter he would
Twitter lo
fire him What do you  David Bravo is saying
echaba Qué te está diciendo David Bravo
to you
a ti
there
ahí
or you're stupid or a bad person, I mean there are only
o tonto o mala persona o sea solo hay
two, that's it, I've said it many
dos es que es eso yo lo he dicho muchas
times, eh, I've said many times either
veces eh yo he dicho muchas veces o
Dallas is very stupid or he's very stupid or he's a
Dallas es muy tonto o es muy tonto o es
very bad person and here the lawyer makes it
muy mala persona y aquí el abogado se lo
clear. It's obvious that it's not
deja claro Es evidente que no es
freedom of expression, it's a great
libertad de expresión es buenísimo un
channel, man, I mean, nobody
canal tío o sea nadie
absolutely nobody, no
absolutamente nadie ningún medio de
media outlet that isn't his friend, the one from
comunicación que no sea su amigo el de
faa, okay, eh,
faa vale eh
nobody's going to start calling David
nadie se va a poner a llamar al David
Bravo to see what's come of it, eh, a
Bravo para ver en qué ha quedado eh una
lawsuit, I mean, this network if I'm not mistaken,
demanda o sea este red si no me equivoco
correct me if I'm wrong. This is
corregirme si me equivoco Este es el
Pablo Iglesias' channel,
canal de Pablo Iglesias
man, I mean literally the lawyer in the
tío o sea literalmente el abogado en los
proceedings that interest him because
procedimientos que le interesan porque
there are some who forget. But well,
hay algunos que se les olvida Pero bueno
we'll talk about that in a
ya hablaremos de eso dentro de unos
few days, he literally dedicates himself to
cuantos de días literalmente se dedica a
walking around all the media outlets
pasearse por por todos los medios de
that allow him to
comunicación que le dejan a darle
spread his rulings and apart from that, I
difusión a sus sentencias y aparte me
remember that when he won this lawsuit, he went
acuerdo que cuando ganó esta demanda fue
to the press to say that it was a
a la prensa a decir que era una
pioneering ruling, I mean, the lawyer
sentencia pionera o sea el abogado lo
wants to be famous in some way, a
que quiere ser famosito de alguna forma
famous influencer who gives sscas, not for
influencer famosito que da sscas no para
people  just like this one who is impressed
gente así como este que se impresiona
because I say this he takes it out he takes it out
porque diga esto se la saca se la saca
no he doesn't take it out it's not even a
no no se la saca ni siquiera es una
pioneering sentence the lawsuits for the
sentencia pionera las demandas por
right to honor in Tómbola in save the
derecho al honor en Tómbola en salva las
gossip magazines that has been going on for a
revistas del corazón eso lleva ya toda
lifetime it's been going on let's say it's older
la vida es lleva vamos es más antiguo
than walking for adante in What is a
que anda para adante en Qué es
pioneer in What is in against a
pionero en Qué es en un contra un
youtuber with his cap backward or rather
youtuber con la gorra para atrás o sea
in What is a
en Qué es
pioneer or rather these lawsuits for the right
pionero o sea estas demandas de derecho
to were not invented by bis Bravo eh I mean well there's
a no las ha inventado bis Bravo eh o sea
no need to go into sálvame
pues anda que no hay meteros en sálvame
And you'll see how many lawsuits like this they have
Y veréis cuántas demandas de esta tienen
How many convictions like this have they had for having
Cuántas condenas de esta han tenido por
insulted I don't know who for having
haber insulto a no sé quién por habber
insulted I don't know how much I mean there's nothing pioneering about it
insulto a no sé cuánto o sea de pionero
but it's not even
no tiene nada pero es que ni siquiera lo
pioneering on YouTube it's that on
tiene pionero en YouTube es que en
YouTube there are already a lot of people who have a
YouTube ya hay mucha gente que tiene un
lot of these lawsuits for rights
montón de demandas de estas de derecho
if this is what there is if people
si es que esto es lo que hay si la gente
can take it happens that normally well
puede tomar se pasa que normalmente pues
people don't do it because it's very
la gente no lo hace porque es muy
expensive you know and it takes a long time because then
costoso sabes y tarda mucho porque luego
you tell me
tú me dices a mí
eh For example when the delo has  the
eh Por ejemplo cuando el delo tenga el
trial with this Imagine that he wins
juicio con este Imagínate que le gana
Okay, well it will have been between the trial, the
Vale pues habrán pasado entre juicio
sentence, between the time the cartel opens
sentencia entre que le abre el cartelo A
Maybe 3 years and now he appeals, I don't know
lo mejor 3 años y ahora recurre no sé
what What are people going to care about the
qué Qué le va a importar a la gente el
result of the trial, do you understand that?
resultado del juicio me entiendes eso ya
You already sue, I mean, for example, the
tú demandas o sea yo por ejemplo a la
people that I have sued is because they have
gente que he demandado es porque se han
gone too far and I can't pass it to them, I
pasado y no se lo puedo pasar no se lo
can't allow it,
puedo permitir me
anyone understands It is evident that it
entiende para cualquiera Es evidente que
is not freedom here here nauter
no es libertad aquí aquí a a nauter le
has missed putting the clip of David
ha faltado poner el clip de de David
Bravo very right saying any
Bravo acertadisimo diciendo cualquier
person with an average intelligence would
persona con una inteligencia media
understand that this Well, well, it is not
entendería que esto Pues bueno no forma
part of reality, right? Then oas
parte de la realidad no Entonces oas lo
knows perfectly well what what based on what
sabe perfectamente lo que qué basado qué
based on the lawyer What does he do or maybe it
basado el abogado Qué hace o a lo mejor
is that he does not have an average intelligence, I
es que no tiene una inteligencia media
think that there is what the CP of
creo que ahí ahí ha faltado el CP de
David Bravo was missing telling him yes Maybe maybe
David Bravo diciéndole sí Igual igual sí
you are missing something in your brain laughing
que te falta algo en el cerebro reírse
at Pablo Franco is usually bad business he
de Pablo Franco suele ser mal negocio
wins a large part, let's see, I do not laugh at him,
gana gran parte a ver yo no me río de él
I laugh at the charges they want to
yo me río de los cargos que quieren
put on me because I am 100% sure that
ponerme porque estoy 100% seguro que
I am under my legitimacy But well, we
estoy bajo mi legitimidad Pero bueno
will pay if he does
pagaremos si hace
missing that you are 100% sure that it is
falta que está 100% seguro de que está
under your legitimacy of what to insult
bajo su legitimidad de qué de insultar
the delox But well we will pay if
al delox Pero bueno pagaremos si hace
necessary and I am quite quite sure okay Okay well you
falta y estoy bastante bastante seguro
are not so sure
vale Vale pues no estás tan seguro
because on Twitter you posted this no eh I
porque en Twitter has puesto esto no eh
can lose perfectly if there is a trial
puedo perder perfectamente si hay juicio
I am not like the others who believe themselves
yo no soy como los otros que se creen
winners of everything but it is what there is in
vencedores de todo pero es lo que hay de
fact there is one Look at
hecho hay un Mira
this even if it reaches me Even if I lose
este aunque me llegue Aunque pierda
even if I have to pay I am not going to stop
aunque tenga que pagar no voy a dejar de
saying whatever I want if you dedicate yourself to
decirlo lo que quiera si te dedicas a la
criticism and being controversial this can
crítica y a ser polémico esto puede
happen but I do defend freedom of
pasar pero yo sí defiendo la libertad de
expression until the end Oh friend
expresiv hasta el final Ah amigo que
when they sue you you understand that
cuando te demandan a ti entiendes que
this is something that is what those of us who are
esto pues es una cosa que es a lo que
dedicated
estamos expuestos los que nos dedicamos
to this are exposed to Ah friend okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay I mean
a esto Ah amigo vale vale vale
nothing happens
vale vale vale vale o sea no pasa nada
no laser yes dem I am happy the
no láser si dem estoy contento salió la
sentence came out not that you have looked for it
sentencia no que tú te lo has buscado
churra that
churra que
what we told you what I told you was It was
que lo que te dijimos lo que yo te dije
animus retor Candy was animus
era Era animus retor Candy era animus
retor Candy no the favorite word gives you
retor Candy no la palabra favorita te da
life Miare his mother and his family
la vida miare su madre y su familia
appealed in the
recurriera en la
senten left everything very well tied not
senten dejado todo muy bien atado no dos
twice without Ar and well we'll see
veces sin Ar y bueno ya veremos la
season 3 without arroo because let's wait a
season 3 sin arroo porque esperemos un
couple of months to see what happens the
par de mesecitos a ver qué pasa el
guy put on I'm not going to put an adjective
tío se puso no le voy a poner adjetivo
okay to what he did but the guy
vale a lo que hizo pero el tío
literally aarte that he sent to his whatever he has
literalmente aarte de que envió a sus lo
there in the chat I don't know if they
que tenga ahí en el chat No no sé si
call the followers or directly
llaman los seguidores o directamente
hater of Dallas he didn't send them to go to the
hater del Dallas no los mandó a ir a los
two videos that I uploaded reading The
dos vídeos que subí yo leyendo La
sentence to comment man, I mean
sentencia a comentar tío o sea
literally this guy who thinks he
literalmente este chico que cree que
can do this okay And who thinks that
esto lo puede hacer vale Y que cree que
nothing is going to happen to him made a live
no le va a pasar nada en hizo un directo
reacting to my video reading a
reaccionando a mi vídeo leyendo una
sentence and sent people to
sentencia y mandó a la gente a a
comment And he thinks
comentar Y se cree que lo puede
he can do it reading The sentence I believe
hacer él leyendo La sentencia yo creo
in my opinion the best video that
según mi opinión el mejor vídeo que ha
Javi Oliveira has made the best Game
hecho Javi oliveira el mejor Game
Over that Javi Oliveira has ever made the game
Over qu ha hecho Javi oliveira el game
over That's how I would do Game Over That's how they
over Así mismo yo haría Game Over Así
condemn you for
mismo que te condenen por
insults What does that take me down
insultos En qué me desmonta eso
boy even tiktok of this no I would do
chico incluso tiktok de esto no yo haría
even tiktok of that tells people you
incluso tiktok de eso le dice a la gente
know the audience
sabes la audiencia
small province there will be time  for
provincia pequeña ya habrá tiempo para
the enjoyment good video sup likee I think
el disfrute buen vídeo sup likee yo creo
and he himself answering but I mean a
y él mismo contestando pero o sea una
person that I have blocked from
persona a la que tengo bloqueada de
everywhere starts
todas partes se pone a
writing to me and sending people from his
escribirme y a mandar a la gente de su
community to write to me and it's not that
comunidad a que me escriba y ya no es
but also he himself as they
eso sino Además él mismo como le
suspend his Twitter accounts I have
suspenden las cuentas de Twitter Tengo
several times that he has responded to me
varias veces las que él me ha respondido
on twit telling me right now you have the
a twit sea diciéndome ya mismo tienes el
trial of this one right now you have the trial of the
juicio de este ya mismo tienes el juicio
other one that you are going to lose it
del otro que lo vas a perder
also interesting for the future It will be
también interesante para un futuro Será
very
muy
interesting but then you guys
interesante pero es que luego ustedes
believe this is a question eh you
creéis esto es una pregunta eh ustedes
think that in court it will be the
cree que en el jugado será
same you think that in court It will
igual ustedes cree que en el jugado Se
get the same from here funny and
pondrá igual de aquí de gracioso y a
say Haha Javi Dani a kiss 10 months do
decir Jaja Javi Dani un beso 10 mesecito
you think that in court he will behave the
creéis que en el juzgado se comportará
same like that Oh based it's me no Look
igual así de Oh basado soy yo no Mira
Javi you've done a gin
Javi te has hecho un gin
over I think it's the best video it's the
over creo que es el mejor vídeo es el
best Game Over that Javi
mejor Game Over que ha hecho Javi
oliveira has done when justice is done The
oliveira cuando se hace justicia Yo lo
only thing I hope the only thing I hope
único que espero yo lo único que espero
is that they are not the last
es que no sean las últimas
Ah that I only hope is that they are not the
Ah que yo lo único que espero es que no
last Well look  you where in the end for
última Pues mira tú por dónde al final
now I
de momento a
won't open the mailman with
ti de momento no le abr al cartero con
one let's see how you do when there are two
una a ver cómo lo haces cuando sean dos
or three more that you're missing Still this
o tres más que te faltan Todavía este
year that they're going to arrive to you according to what they
año que te van a llegar según me han
told me eh according to what they told me
dicho eh según me han dicho
eh I mean how you're going to be laughing how
eh o sea cómo te vas a estar riendo cómo
you're going to be laughing like that wishing
te vas a estar riendo así deseándole a
others to lose other people than you
otros que pierdan otra gente que a ti
because the last interaction that I
porque la última interacción que yo
had with him, I eh he hasn't stopped
tengo con él yo eh él no me ha dejado de
mentioning me but my last interaction was
mencionar pero mi última interacción fue
that we each went our own way and
que cada uno fuimos por nuestro lado y
the guy hasn't stopped and the guy there to a
el tío no ha parado y el tío ahí a una
person who ignores him who doesn't say
persona que pasa de él que no le dice
anything to him, more are going to arrive I hope it's not the
nada te van a llegar más Ojalá no sea la
last Well we'll see who
última Bueno ya veremos quién quién
accumulates more yoico that I hope are not
acumula más yoico que espero que no sean
the last carche Abi seriously carche
las últimas carche Abi en serio carche
Abi Abi called me a [ __ ] Abi called me a
Abi Abi me llamó [__] Abi me llamó
[ __ ] cheer up Abi and file
[__] que que se anime Abi y me ponga
a lawsuit against me Avi called me a [ __ ] and carche
una demanda Avi me llamó [__] y carche
I also have a folder here with
tengo yo aquí una carpetita también con
things that he
cositas que él me ha
told me carche carche Jai then you
dicho carche carche Jai entonces tú
carche Abi let's [ __ ] Go that the
carche Abi let's fucking Go que la
rachita don't stop that's the only thing I
rachita no pare eso es lo único que
hope But from here very little of those who
espero Pero de aquí muy poco de las que
have the demands that they had put on
tiene las demandas que tenían puestas
that they had put on Javi No, for me
que tenía puestas Javi No yo para mí
this is a prize, it's a prize, for
esto es es un premio es un premio para
me this is the enjoyment no, this this clip
mí esto es el disfrute no este este clip
is great to put on every
es buenísimo para ir poniéndoselo cada
time the postman doesn't open it and Javi I
vez que no le abre el cartero e Javi me
see all the lord of your channels I love you and I
veo todo el lord de tus canales te amo y
love how you
me encanta como
think guide ent FR t in the sanctuary
piensas guía ent FR t en el santuario
well there will be something very soon
bueno algo habrá dentro de muy poquito
this for This, for me, is a prize, it's
esto para Esto para mí es un premio es
a enjoyment, man, for me, honestly, it's that what
un disfrute tío a mí yo sinceramente es
these people do, starting
que esto que hacen esta gente de ponerse
to talk to Antonia, starting to
a hablarse con la Antonia de ponerse a
talk to each other, I mean,
hablarse con el otro o sea literalmente
this guy literally made a video in which he
hizo un vídeo este chico en el que
supported another youtuber in which they were going to
apoyaba a otro youtuber en el que iban a
collaborate to close my channels, okay, I
colaborar para cerrarme los canales vale
mean, I have everything saved, he already, I'm
o sea lo tengo todo guardadito él ya yo
not going to tell you anything in advance, but he
no os voy a adelantar nada pero él lo
will have to explain it, but I'm going to
tendrá que explicar pero a mí me va a
love to see it if he explains it the same in the juel,
encantar verlo si en el juel lo explica
eh Because I get the impression that
igual eh Porque me va la impresión de
the videos when we put them up are not
que los vídeos cuando los pongamos no
going to be the same, but of course it is  that I have
van a ser iguales pero claro es que yo
n't made
este chico no lo he vuelto a hacer
any videos about this guy or mentioned him in two
ningún vídeo ni lo he mencionado en dos
or three years of course So I don't understand
o tres años claro Entonces no entiendo
what he's going to claim, a fight,
qué es lo que va a alegar él una pelea
an argument, or is he going to pull that I
una discusión o va a tirar de que me
messed with him 3 years ago before reaching an
metí con él hace 3 años antes de llegar
agreement to not mention each other anymore. I mean,
al acuerdo de no mencionarnos más O sea
he's his prize, that's his, that's what
que él es su premio que es su que es lo
makes me happy, really, this
que le hace feliz a mí realmente a este
guy now that they condemn him, it wouldn't matter to me
chico ahora que lo condenen me daría
Exactly the same I mean, what would change in
Exactamente igual O sea qué cambiaría en
my life if this person is completely
mi vida si esta persona es completamente
irrelevant, you know, and I'm not going to start
irrelevante sabes y yo no me voy a poner
talking to people who don't like
a hablarme con gente que a la que le
this guy Because
caiga mal este chico Porque este chico
a lot of people can dislike this guy and
le puede caer mal a un montón de gente y
I'm not going to start talking to all the
yo no me voy a poner hablarme con toda
people who don't get along with him or who
la gente que se lleve mal él o con quien
he has
él tenga
problems with, you know, I mean, No, my life is not
problemas sabes o sea No mi vida no se
based on who doesn't get along with this
basa en quién se lleve mal con este
man, I don't even know who he is, I
hombre no sé ni quién
know who he is by the s, his name, by the
es sé quién es por la s su nombre por la
lawsuit until until the delos didn't
demanda hasta que hasta que el delos no
file the lawsuit, I don't know his name but
le puso la demanda no se su nombre pero
well, I know, we'll see the explanation
bueno yo sé ya veremos la explicación
that
que
gives the enjoyment of the
da el disfrute de de la carrera de
YouTube career The truth Now I  I'm glad he
YouTube La verdad Ahora me alegro que él
eats [ __ ] it's you the truth eat
come [__] seas tú la verdad come
[ __ ] well well
[__] bueno
Well eat [ __ ] he called me there
Bueno come [__] me ha llamado ahí
well on top of that I went to investigate
bueno encima me he metido a investigar
a little to see who is delox's lawyer
un poquito a ver quién es el abogado de
who must be the same lawyer that
delox que debe ser el mismo abogado que
jav oliveira has and and I see that in his
tiene el jav oliveira y y veo que en su
Twitter profile picture he has a picture
foto de perfil de Twitter tiene una foto
with Fran it's really hard eh outrageous
con Fran cuesta barbaridad eh barbaridad
This is the lawyer Pablo Franco this one
Este es el abogado el Pablo Franco este
here this
de aquí este
Franco
Franco
is the one also accused by the
es la que también acusada por la
Spanish prosecutor's office Here he also put his foot in it
española Aquí metido la pata
for publishing a photo of a
también por publicar una foto de una
minor it's
menor
not that he's a barbri this is that he's a
no es que es barbri esto es que es
barbri dude okay people who have It's that
barbri tío vale gente que tiene Es que
this is something that they're saying the
esto es una cosa que están diciendo el
other day I saw him challenge the cani tillero
otro día se lo vi retar al cani tillero
that I don't know if it will sound familiar to you okay Sure Look
que no sé si os sonará vale Claro Mira
here this account coincidentally also
aquí est cuenta casualmente también
saying the same thing
diciendo lo mismo
okay investigated spreading the video of
vale investigada difundir el vídeo de
a gang rape of two minors in
una violación grupal a dos menores en
Valencia of course eh Cristina has not
Valencia claro es que eh Cristina no ha
spread the video of any
difundido el vídeo de ninguna
rape then of course this I don't know
violación entonces claro esto yo no sé
if Vanessa a kiss Cristina is
si Vanessa un beso Cristina está
suing eh Cristina is they are
demandando eh Cristina está están
suing absolutely everyone who
demandando absolutamente a todos los que
is insinuating this  kind of things no
están insinuando este tipo de cosas no
eh Cristina what she published and you have an
eh Cristina lo que publicó y tenéis una
interview that utbh did on her
entrevista que le ha hecho utbh en su
channel there she explains it without problem
canal ahí lo explica ella sin problema
more extensively
más extensamente
was a case of some girls apparently
fue un caso de unas chicas por lo visto
said they were raped but then
que dijeron ser violadas pero luego por
apparently these girls on their
lo visto estas chicas en su cuenta de
Instagram account said it was a lie and that they
Instagram dijeron que era mentira y que
wanted to become famous I don't know what and
querían hacerse famosas no sé qué y
Cristina published on her Twitter the video
Cristina publicó en su Twitter el vídeo
of those girls saying that which was a
de esas chicas diciendo eso que era
lie on her Instagram account in
mentira en su cuenta de Instagram en
public with their faces
público con las caras
bald no one accuses her
peladas no le acusa una la fiscalía
of
española de
that it is not like that but well laser if you
eso no es así pero bueno láser si tú eso
can
lo puedes
prove that you have messed with Pablo Franco or
probar te has metido con Pablo franco o
whatever It's that look at you eh look at you eh Yes they
sea Es que fíjate tú eh fíjate tú eh Sí
explain it in the live of
lo explican en el en el directo de de
utbh well utbh on his main channel
utbh bueno utbh en su canal principal
has the
tiene la
full interview but you start
entrevista completa pero te pones a
messing with Cristina continue to defame
meterte con Cristina seguí a difamar a
Cristina follow buddy to mess with
Cristina seguí colega para meterte con
Pablo Franco
Pablo Franco
and then the lawsuit will be
y luego la demanda será culpa de
dala's fault Hey you are having a
dala Oye estáis teniendo una
parallel conversation
conversación paralela
[ __ ] [ __ ] it's
[__]
going to get very brown
[__] se va liar muy parda
eh Hey  I want to know what's going on
eh Oye Quiero saber qué pasa
[ __ ] it [ __ ] it
jod No jodas
Ah well that is reportable Yeah yeah
Ah pues eso sí que es denunciable Sí sí
but come on Ah this is a very
pero vamos Ah esto es una cosa muy
strong thing I can't say
fuerte no puedo decir yo
anything about that I can't I can't say anything
Nada eso no puedo no puedo decir yo nada
but it is a very
pero es una cosa muy
strong thing no if no that [ __ ] well or in
fuerte no si no eso [__] pues o en
March or in February when it's
marzo o en febrero cuando sea
clear I think Javi is going to come at the
claro yo creo que Javi va a venir a
end of January or beginning of February
finales de enero o principios de febrero
eh Javi Oliveira eh I'm going with
eh Javi oliveira eh yo voy con
Javi at the end of January beginning of
Javi a finales de enero principios de
February I don't know I think maybe yes maybe
febrero No lo sé creo puede que sí puede
yes that it will
que sí que
be in the first trimester I'm definitely
sea en el primer trimestre seguro
going Yes because we need a
voy Sí porque necesitamos
nanny Oh we need one we need a Nani
niñera Ay necesitamos una necesitamos
no me no me don't tell me no me it
una Nani no me no me no me leres no me
's another guy [ __ ] I don't seem like
es otro tío [__] Yo hoy hoy no parezco
I'm talking well about everything God But
yo estoy hablando bien de todo Dios Pero
Javi is a guy you see him in person and he
Javi es un tío que lo ves en persona y
's super polite dude yes he's an
es super educado tío sí es un tío
intelligent guy I mean a guy from the
inteligente o sea un tí de es un tío de
neighborhood whose mother gave him the beatings
barrio que la madre le metió las hostias
that she had to give him in her time no me he
que le tuvo que meter a su tiempo no me
should have given it badly he
me tenía que haber metido mal se la [__]
screwed up the poor thing many times and he
se quedó corta la pobre muchas veces y
met a woman who also
se encontró con una mujer que también le
gave him the beatings that she had to  put in
metió las hostias que le tuvo que meter
your time yes and what he is but he's a
a su tiempo sí y lo que es pero es un
hard worker eh I know a person I
currante eh yo conoc una persona Yo
know a lady who has known his
conozco una señora que conoce a su
family all her life damn
familia de toda la vida ostia siempre
Fran always tells this in public man no and I
cuenta el Fran esto en público tío no y
always forget to ask her Who
siempre se me olvida preguntarle Quién
is the
es la
lady it was funny Because I was
señora fue fue curioso Porque yo estuve
in
en
Seville for one thing and and I was with Irene
Sevilla una cosa y y estaba con Irene
Villa talking and a lady came
Villa hablando y vino una señora se
sat down at the table sits down the lady says
sentó en la mesa se sienta la tía dice
hey Fran can I sit down he says yes
hola Fran me puedo sentar dice sí se
sits down he says hey hey have you had a fight
sienta dice oye heo te has peleado con
with Javier Oliveira who is a very good
con Javier oliveira que es muy buen
guy I've known him for many
chaval que lo conozco desde hace muchos
years that I don't know I mean [ __ ] such a hard worker
años que no s digo [__] tal trabajador
a lady must be friends with his mother or
una señora sería amiga de su madre o
something and I was amazed I was amazed
algo y me quedé flipado me quedé flipado
and then Look it's true that
y luego Fíjate que es verdad que todo el
everyone you talk to says he's a
mundo que hablas te dice es un tío
polite guy when when you talk to him in very
educado cuando cuando lo tratas en
polite people
personas educadísimos
with
con
I heard 5 years 6 years ago he didn't know how to
escuchado ha hace 5 años 6 años no sabía
speak the bastard No that's true he didn't know how to
hablar el cabrón No eso verdad no sabía
speak but he has worried And the truth
hablar pero se ha preocupado Y la verdad
is he's doing well he's doing very well I haven't
es que le va bien le va muy bien yo no
worried to speak better
me he preocupado para hablar mejor
you know what's going on eh They're me  bringing out the
sabéis Qué pasa eh Me están sacando los
colors apart that they are dismantling I mean
colores aparte que están desmantel O sea
literally I no no it's that I didn't know how to
literalmente yo no no es que no supiera
speak it's that I had a very very very
hablar es que tenía un acento muy muy
closed accent very
muy cerrado muy
closed I didn't leave the neighborhood and then and
cerrado no salía del barrio y luego
and
e y
then Of course it's true that maybe
luego Claro si que es verdad que a lo
in person I don't peres Of course I don't go no I don't
mejor en persona no peres Claro no voy
go fighting and challenging
no no voy peleándome y retando
debating people challenging people
debatiendo a la gente retando a la gente
to debate they haven't taken my colors out here a little of
a debate no me han saca aquí un poco los
course let's see it's that of course The
colores claro a ver es que claro La
Movida is that well well you Here you have to
Movida es que bueno pues tú Aquí tienes
be more aggressive of course obviously
que ser más cañero claro evidentemente
but no no no the seat has been
pero no no no el asento se ha se ha
corrected a little in the sense that
corregido un poco en el sentido de que
here I spend more days with people from outside
aquí me pego más días con gente de fuera
of Seville than from here and well
de de Sevilla que que de aquí y bueno
family well this is the news the
familia pues esta es la novedad la
truth is that I would like to be able to tell you
verdad es que me gustaría poder contaros
something more but at the moment I can't
algo más pero de momento no puedo
tell you something else okay but they continue their
contaros algo más vale pero siguen su
course the two demands continue their course
curso siguen las dos demandas su curso
yes it's true that delox
sí que es verdad que delox
eh put his foot in it a bit in saying no no
eh metio un poco la pata en decir que no
yes it has reached you Don't play dumb
no sí te ha llegado No te hagas el loco
because there I was a bit like well well well well well
que ahí me quedé yo un poco como bueno
well Of course
bueno bueno bueno bueno bueno Claro
because you don't know what  you're talking
porque no sabes yo lo que estás hablando
and well he'll be sure and of course
y bueno estará seguro y claro es que de
what happens is that he doesn't understand
los lo que pasa es que él no entiende de
judicial procedures because he's never
Procedimientos judiciales porque nunca
gotten into trouble of suing or being
est ha metido en lío del é demandar ni
sued or anything and he believed
de que lo demanden ni nada y él se creía
that since the other person had already received the
que como ya le había llegado al otro el
burofax, well that was like it had
burofax pues eso era como que le había
arrived at the beginning of the procedure, I do
llegado al principio del procedimiento
n't know, a roll because he told me but
no sé un rollo porque él me dijo pero
how come it hasn't arrived if the
cómo que no le ha llegado si le llegó el
burofax arrived, I don't know what it's not a mess it's a mess it's a
buruan no s qué no es un lío es un lío
mess But well he was wrong about that
es un lío Pero bueno se equivocó en eso
but anyway,
pero vamos que de todas maneras que no
nothing's happening, the lawsuits have been filed,
pasa nada que las demandas están puestas
both of them, I can guarantee it because he's my
las dos os lo garantizo yo porque es mi
lawyer because I've seen it, I can
abogado porque yo lo he
guarantee it because he's my lawyer and
os lo garantizo porque es mi abogado y
because I've
porque yo lo he
seen it. Who should sue Cristina to
visto A quiénes demandar a Cristina
continue, well, she has sued several
seguir pues ha demandado a varios medios
of these media outlets for rectification, lawsuits for
de estos de rectificación demandas de
rectification, but apart from that, they are
estas de rectificación pero aparte están
also suing, they are also seeing who
demandando también están viendo quien
affirms because there are people who are
Afirma porque hay gente que está
maliciously affirming after the
afirmando con maldad después de que los
media have rectified that she
medios hayan rectificado que ella
published the photos like what she said  the
publicó la fotos como lo que ha dicho el
leren that she published the photos of a
leren que ella publicó las fotos de un
minor like buo well and ad is already
menores como buo bueno y ad ya lo está
doing it with malice with the intention of
haciendo con maldad con la intención de
[ __ ] Not because you are wrong I don't know
de [__] No porque te equivoques no sé
what you know but well
qué sabes pero bueno
eh let's get a little into the subject the
eh vamos a entrar un poco en materia la
truth because the day the day was given
verdad porque el día se el día se dio
Movidito
Movidito
today the day was given Movidito today first
hoy el día se dio Movidito hoy primer
gossip of the year strong
salseo del año fuerte
eh survey
eh encuesta
with Felipe
con con Felipe
repulsive guy eh repulsive what
tío repulsivo eh repulsivo lo de
Felipe did very repulsive what Felipe did
Felipe muy repulsivo lo de Felipe
eh Let's see if I missed something I
eh A ver por si me he perdido algo le he
missed luare that I compile everything from
perdido luare que me lo recopile todo de
gref that damn fraudster of
gref ese maldito defraudador de
[ __ ] well the story begins
[__] bueno la historia comienza
when Antonio mur uploads my Excel of the
cuando Antonio mur sube mi Excel de los
days that I have played fortnite in
días que he jugado a fortnite en
But this responding to the thread no luare
Pero esto respondiendo al hilo no luare
the first thing
lo primero
no I mean this is responding to the thread
no o sea esto es respondiendo al hilo
not a small tweet that has only gotten
no un pequeño tweet que solo ha pillado
20 million impressions great job
20 millones de impresiones gran trabajo
by Antonio mur Well that doing the
el de Antonio mur Pues eso haciendo el
Excel of the days that I have played fortnite
Excel de los días que he jugado fortnite
and the one and the days that I have not played
y el que y los días que no he jugado
fortnite  that this frank and says that is to
fortnite que esta francua y dice es
say that you document us that degrez
decir que nos documentas que degrez
complies with Ah no no okay okay he goes with
cumple con Ah no no vale vale va con
Fran legality he lives happily he can continue
Fran legalidad vive feliz puede seguir
visiting his family and friends he doesn't have to
visitando a su familia y amigos no tiene
give half of his money to
que dar la mitad de su dinero a los
thieving politicians and he can save for
políticos ladrones y puede ahorrar para
the future apart from giving jobs to
el futuro aparte de darle trabajo a
others I don't know you but instead of
otros no te conozco pero en vez de
worrying about other people's jobs and their
preocuparte del trabajo de otros y de su
lives worry about your own better, I mean,
vida preocúpate de lo tuyo mejor o sea
forceful tweet from Frank costs eh Partly
tweet contundente de Frank cuesta eh En
defending him than the politicians and you
defendiéndolo que los políticos y tú lo
defend him the logic is brutal answers
defiendes la lógica es brutal contesta
Fran huesta gref does not collect public money he does
Fran huesta gref no cobra dinero público
not have an official car he does not collect
no tiene coche oficial no cobra de los
other people's taxes he does not have several
impuestos de otros no tiene varios
salaries and above all he is a
sueldos y sobre todo es un empresario
private businessman your logic is [ __ ] a
privado tu lógica es de [__] un
video with half a million views in
vídeo con medio millón de visitas en
trends in which basically I have not
tendencias en el que básicamente yo no
seen it but I am not going to see it now
lo he visto pero no lo voy a ver ahora
but I do not know if someone can summarize for me
pero no sé si alguien me puede resumir
what Frank says out here he should leave and
lo que Frank dice aquí fuera se vaya y
that the people who leave should do
que la gente que se vaya fuera pues hace
well Why do people have to mess
bien Por qué la gente se tiene que meter
with youtubers with the streamers or in
con los youtubers con Los streamers o en
this case with deg Simply because they
este caso con deg Simplemente porque
earn money and go  to another country with
ganan dinero y se van a a otro país con
this guy really is that really
este tío de verdad es que de verdad
explaining the subject petting a
explicando el tema acariciando a un
pig arrives here at the to the to the door
cerdo llega aquí a la a la a la puerta
this one and I don't even know what this is they are not
esta de y no sé ni qué es esto no son
peacocks and what will they do Here these
pavos reales y de qué harán Aquí estos
wretches me when I go to Spain
desgraciados yo cuando voy a España a
sometimes well at Christmas to see my
veces bueno en Navidades por ver a mi
family And such But it's because I have
familia Y tal Pero es porque tengo
commitments, I mean I have
compromisos o sea tengo compromisos de
work commitments to say [ __ ] well I have to
de trabajo de decir [__] pues tengo
be at this game or I have to go
que estar en tal partido o tengo que ir
to a Draft I mean the Kings League what it
a un Draft O sea la Kings League lo que
did to me last year is it's
a mí me ha hecho el año pasado es es una
crazy people think that I measure
locura la gente se cree que yo eh mido
the days and I say Well then I'm
los días y digo Bueno pues la la mitad
going to spend half of them Enjoying myself in Spain
me los voy a tirar Disfrutando en España
don't get me wrong if I'm happy in
no te equivoques si yo estoy feliz en
Andorra and I think I'm one of the youtubers
andorra y creo que soy de los youtubers
who does the most things here to Rubius to gref
que más cosas hace aquí al Rubius a gref
to the people who don't know Let's see let's see
a la gente que se no A ver a ver a ver
that either eh gref or I mean you're not
eso ya tampoco eh gref o sea de tonto
going to be stupid either there aren't many
tampoco me vas a tampoco no hay muchos
days that you stick to the Setup in
días que tú te lo pegas en el Setup de
Murcia because you feel like it because you're
murcia porque te apetese porque estás
there with friends with your family or
allí con amigos con tu familia o lo que
whatever and we  we can work wherever we are, that
sea y nosotros podemos trabajar donde
is, me having a computer and
estemos o sea yo teniendo un ordenador y
all the equipment set up, if I had
todo el equipo montado si yo tuviera
another house in Chipiona with the Setup
otra casa en chipiona con el Setup
set up, okay, maybe I have a more
montado vale a lo mejor tengo más
powerful Setup where I spend the most time,
potente el Setup donde más tiempo estoy
but then I have another one there that's also
pero luego tengo allí otro que también
good, okay, a good computer, also
está bien vale un buen ordenador también
some spotlights, a good microphone, so I
unos focos un buen micrófono pues lo
can do it wherever I want. Okay, but don't
puedo hacer donde quiera Vale pero no me
come to me with that story that no, no, that it
vengas con el rollo de que no no de que
's just a coincidence that your Cents coincide, I
es casual de que te coincidan los Cent
think it's 190 days, let's see that, do
creo que son 190 días a ver eso
n't laugh at me either,
tampoco a ver de reírte de mí tampoco
buddy, he's gone over there, okay, eh, you
colega se ha ido para allá vale eh Tú
've been collecting, you've been
has estado cobrando tú has estado
collecting allowances and they've been
cobrando paguitas y se han estado
spending the money on [ __ ], okay,
gastando el dinero en gilipolleces vale
to say that a guy who looks like
para decir que un tío que tiene el
me is called Mari Carmen, I'm not
aspecto mío se llama Mari Carmen no
participating in this series of debates because,
entro en esta serie de debates porque
as I explained on El Hormiguero back in the day,
como expliqué en su día El Hormiguero
which I'm going to say here, I had the balls to
que lo voy a decir aquí tuve los [__]
go to El Hormiguero so Pablo Motos could
de ir al Hormiguero a que Pablo motos me
ask me about Andorra, about
preguntara sobre andorra sobre los
taxes, when the issue was at its hottest.
impuestos cuando más caliente estaba el
When Rubius moved to Andorra and
tema Cuando Rubius se mudó a andorra y
I noticed that public opinion
yo notaba que la opinión pública nos
was eating us up, I had the  balls
estaba comiendo y yo tuve los [__]
because there's no other way to say it I had
porque no se puede decir otra forma tuve
the balls to go to the program with the highest
los cojon zos de ir al programa con más
audience in Spain to stand up for
audiencia de España a dar la cara por
our guild and for the group of
nuestro gremio y por el grupo de
streamers that I believed we had to
streamers que que creía que teníamos que
defend and I consider that the explanation
defender y Considero que la explicación
I gave there was more than enough and
que di all fue más que suficiente y yo
there I basically explained that this is a
allí básicamente expliqué que esto es un
moral debate that we're never going to get
debate moral que jamás vamos a llegar a
anywhere because there will be people who
ningún sitio porque Habrá gente que le
think it's good that it doesn't seem good that we have to
parezca bien que le parezca mal que
put the conversation in
tenemos que poner la conversación en
another type of
otro tipo
but you know that apart from the fact that it
de pero es que sabes que que aparte de
's a moral debate
que es un debate moral
apart from it being a moral debate that is
aparte de que sea un debate moral que
never going to get anywhere the
nunca se va a llegar a ningún sitio la
people who are against what
gente que está en contra de de lo que
others do with their money think
hacen los demás con su dinero piensan
this way because it's not their money or I mean those
así porque no es su dinero o sea esa
same people who point to gref have
misma gente que señalan a gref tienen
two options one or when
dos opciones vale una o bien que cuando
they two options in the event that
ellos dos opciones en el caso de que
one day they manage to earn the same amount of
consigan algún día ganar los mismos
money, for example, imagine fate an al
dineros vale por ejemplo imag fate un al
El capo an ibai or some of these no eh
El capo un ibai o alguno de estos no eh
one one option is when
una una opción es en el momento que
they manage to reach those amounts
ellos consiguen llegar a esas cantidades
of income they do sl or they do the same
de ingresos se hacen sl o hacen lo mismo
and suddenly they become  from the right they
y de repente se vuelven de derecha se
become eh of another way of thinking they
vuelven eh de otra manera de pensar se
leave Andorra and such or they eat it like
van andorra y tal o se lo comen como
ales The boss for having talked so much
ales El capo por haber hablado tanto
many times that happens eh Many times it happens
muchas veces pasa eso eh Muchas veces
that you have a very big little mouth and
pasa que tienes la boquita muy grande y
you have the little mouth that they give you a lot they
tienes la boquita que te las dan mucho
don't give you much chest thumping and this I won't
no te dan mucho golpe de pecho y esto no
do this I don't know how much this no I do
lo haré esto no sé cuánto esto no yo
n't get involved here I don't know what And
aquí no me meto yo aquí no sé qué Y
then you have to screw yourself when you
luego te tienes que [__] cuando los
want to do them and there's something that you can't
quieres hacer y hay algo que no puedes
do because you've said a thousand times that you weren't
hacer porque has dicho mil veces que no
going to do it and you have to screw yourself
lo ibas a hacer y te tienes que [__]
to keep your word and you screw yourself or I
para mantener tu palabra y te jodes o
mean I've seen eh I've seen many cases
sea lo he visto eh he visto muchos casos
of people who I tell you I'm not going to be
de gente que que te digo yo no voy a ser
anymore I'm not going to talk about this subject
nunca más no voy a hablar de este tema
of these subjects I'm never going to talk about them I'm
de estos temas no voy a hablar nunca me
disgusted by people who talk about these
dan asco la gente que hablan de estos
subjects I don't know H topics of gossip or of or
temas yo que sé H temas de salseo o de o
topics delicate topics that get a lot of
de temas temas delicados que den muchas
views or whatever I'm never going to talk
visitas o lo que sea nunca voy a hablar
about this subject I'm never going to talk about this
de este tema nunca voy a hablar de este
subject you're never going to see that my channel
tema nunca me vais a ver que mi canal se
talks about these subjects and then when you
hablen de estos temas y ya luego cuando
're watching the others  putting on your
está viendo a los demás poniéndose las
boots and you don't because you've acted like a
botas y tú no por habert las dado de
moralist well you [ __ ] yourself and you get angry and
moralista pues te jodes y te da coraje y
you're at home thinking I should have kept my
tú estás en tu casa pensando me tenía
[ __ ] mouth shut and now
que haber callado la [__] boca y ahora
I would be just like everyone else
estaría Yo igual que todos los demás
dealing with this issue but anyway anyway
tratando este tema pero bueno en fin
eh it's very easy to give your opinion on
eh es muy fácil opinar del dinero de los
other people's money okay eh something That you wouldn't do with
demás vale eh algo Que no harías con el
yours and that's it No no Let's
tuyo y
see the requirements what are
punto No no A ver los requisitos qué son
these he hasn't met the requirements no
estos no ha cumplido los requisitos no
well [ __ ] off I have nothing to
pues a tomar por culo no me nada que
talk about it's true that of course he does the
hablar no es que claro hace los días
exact days because he's doing it to
justo porque lo está haciendo para
stay longer man of course he
quedarse más hombre claro es que se ha
went to Andorra it's true that he went to Andorra
ido a andorra es que se ha ido a andorra
to get less taxes off him Of course
para que le quiten menos impuestos Claro
if that's what he did it for or
si es que lo ha hecho para eso o para
why do you think he went to Andorra for
qué te crees que se ha ido andorra para
the mountains it's not that he went for the exact
la montaña no es que se ha ido justo los
days that he has as a requirement of course but
días que tiene de requisito claro pero
if he did it I mean why do you
si es que lo ha hecho o sea para qué te
think he's earning r Chaba instead of
crees que está ganando r chaba en vez de
Murcia well for taxes Of course
murcia pues para los impuestos Claro
because here in Spain it's
porque aquí en España es un robo
legalized robbery Of course if there isn't
legalizado Claro si es que no hay
more at another point of okay if you want to
más en otro punto de vale si quieres
keep these people in your  country well well
retener a esta gente en tu país pues
because I answered Lilo about
bueno pues porque yo contesté a Lilo de
this guy I didn't put it for you because
este chico no os lo puse porque estaba
I was around there okay
yo por ahí vale
but but but but but but but
per pero pero pero pero pero pero le
people really liked the answer I gave
gustó mucho a la gente la respuesta que
people really liked the
di le gustó mucho a la gente la
answer I gave wait I'll put it in
respuesta que le di espera la pongo en
a second if I
un segundito si la
find it if I
encuentro si la
find it if I find it I'll
encuentro si lo encuentro os lo
put it for you
pongo
This is a joke I made with this I
Este es un chiste que hice con esto no
haven't documented the days that
he documentado los días que
turboplane does and in Amarillo which are
turboplane sí y en Amarillo los que
also valid Here is my answer Look
también vale Aquí está mi respuesta Mira
I put the turkey and here is my
yo le puse al pavo y aquí tenéis mi
opinion no I mean you've spent the whole
opinión no O sea que te has pasado todo
year exploding such that you realize
el año estalando talque para darte
that you meet the requirements
cuenta que cumple con los requisitos
to pay taxes wherever you want
para tributar donde le salga de los
but you complain anyway I mean is
[__] pero te quejas igual o sea es
this this thread is what the guy is
que este este hil lo que hace el tío
still doing It could make some sense if he
todavía Podría tener algo de sentido si
had caught that gref didn't meet
si hubiera pillado que gref no cumplía
the requirements if I remember correctly the
con los requisitos si mal no recuerdo el
same kid did it last year and
mismo chaval el año pasado lo hizo y
gref had gone a bit over the days that's why I'm
gref se había pasado un poco de los días
telling you gref that the fact that you
por eso te digo gref que eso de que tú
are a coincidence that it's 190 days is not a
sea casualidad que sean 190 días no es
coincidence you have it  calculated What
casualidad lo tienes calculado Lo que
happens is that last year You were
pasa que el año pasado Te
wrong but you complain anyway and you
equivocaste pero pero te quejas igual y
're giving your opinion about money that isn't
estás opinando de un dinero que no es
yours or that you don't earn because you would prefer that
tuyo ni ganas tú porque preferirías que
any politician waste it on
lo malgastas cualquier político en
prostitutes than that the one who generates it spend it
prostitutas a que se lo gaste el que lo
on giving his family a luxurious life
genera en darle una vida lujosa a su
Because it's not yours and you're
familia Porque no es tuyo y tienes
envious or rather it's literally like that dude
envidia o sea literalmente es así tío
literally the
literalmente el
guy would prefer that greev with his money
tío preferiría que greev con su dinero
was paying taxes in Spain not because
estuviera tributando en España no porque
anything would come to him
a él le fuese llegan nada
or gref's taxes would
ni los impuestos de gref fuesen a
improve the country but he as he's seeing
mejorar el país sino él como está viendo
a kid who doing what he wants
un chaval que haciendo lo que quiere
is earning millions of euros Well he
está ganando millones de euros Pues él
prefers he would prefer that gref with his
prefiere él preferiría que gref con su
money pay taxes in Spain even if it was so that
dinero tributas en España aunque fuera
a politician could take it and
para que cogiera un político y se lo
spend it on prostitutes and
gastara en [__] y
cocaine okay because if here the money in
cocaína vale porque si aquí el dinero en
Spain were managed
España se gestionar
well the whole country would be much
bien todo el país estaría Mucho
better much more in conditions everything
mejor mucho más en condiciones todo a
nobody would be missing anything and so
nadie Le faltaría De nada y no harían
many taxes would not be necessary they need to
falta tantos impuestos hacen falta que
take half of it because they are
te quiten la mitad porque son unos
bullies who waste money badly
abusones que malgastan el dinero mal
okay they waste money badly and do
vale malgastan el dinero mal y hacen
every little thing with it  money that they flip out and
cada cosa con el dinero que flipan y
place the brother-in-law and set up a chiringuito
colocan al cuñado y montan Chiringuito
anyway I'm not going to enter that debate now
en fin no voy a entrar ese debate ahora
okay But he Pablo m would prefer that
vale Pero él el Pablo m preferiría que
any politician spent it on
cualquier político se lo gastara en
giving a salary to his brother-in-law or another on
ponerle un suerdo a su cuñado o otro en
cocaine it doesn't matter but that he doesn't have it
cocaína da igual pero que no lo tenga
gref please don't let the one who
gref por favor que no lo tenga el que lo
earns it have it okay Why Because I don't have it
gana vale Por qué Porque yo no lo tengo
then I envy Pablo with that
entonces me da envidia Pablo con ese
time I'm telling you this now this
tiempo Esto se lo estoy diciendo ya este
Pablo okay Pablo with that time that you've
Pablo vale Pablo con ese tiempo que has
spent on this nonsense you could have
empleado en esta tontería podrías haber
founded a supermarket chain and
fundado una cadena de supermercados y
seven hairdressers and you would have created
siete peluquerías y te hubieras creado
an SL as soon as you had realized
una sl en cuanto te hubieras dado cuenta
that in Spain it is legal to steal from the
que en España Es legal robarle a los
self-employed okay literally it's what
autónomos vale literal es lo que les
happens to everyone that the moment you
pasa a todos que en el momento que tú
undertake instead of wasting
emprendes en vez de haber perdido el
time messing with whoever earns it
tiempo en meterte con el que lo gana
Do it yourself that time that effort you could have
Hazlo tú ese tiempo ese esfuerzo podrías
spent it trying, I who
haberlo empleado en en intentar yo que
know how to undertake okay Eat your brain to see
sé emprender vale Cómete el coco a ver
what you can open to see what you can do
qué puedes abrir a ver qué puedes hacer
to earn money too Okay and
para ganar tú también dinero Vale y en
the moment
el momento que lo
you earned it you would find a way to make one
ganastes te buscarías la forma de hacer
trick to not pay like we
una triquiñuela para no pagar como
pay a lot as self-employed okay because as
pagamos mucho de autónomo vale porque de
self-employed It's that it's legal or rather I do
autónomo Es que es que es legal o sea yo
n't know what I'm going to do the truth because the truth
no sé qué voy a hacer la verdad porque
is that here there aren't many options here
es que aquí no hay muchas opciones aquí
what there is is when you meet the
lo que hay es cuando cumplas los
requirements to create an sl but of course for
requisitos hacer una sl pero claro para
that you have to be like I understand that
eso tienes que ser en plan entiendo que
as and goes and that you have a team of
como y va y que tengas un equipo de
people working and so on no So
gente trabajando y demás no Entonces yo
at the moment I am self-employed but of course
de momento soy autónomo pero claro es
I don't have much of an option because
que yo tampoco tengo mucha opción porque
I don't want to leave Spain Why
yo no me quiero ir de España Por qué
Because I have children If I didn't have my children
Porque tengo hijos Si yo no tuviera mis
If I had taken another
hijos Si me hubiera cogido en otro de la
life like at 30 I would have waited
vida en plan con 30 me hubiera esperado
until the maximum to have children and I would have
al tope para tener hijos y me hubiera
hit it all the possible years
pegado todos los años posibles
surely in surely Not in Andorra
seguramente en seguramente No en andorra
but in Portugal but not in Spain dude I
sino en Portugal pero no en España tío o
mean it doesn't make any sense for them to
sea es que no hay ningún sentido para
take half of you and rob you it's that they have
que te quiten la mitad y te roben es que
legalized and they have normalized
han legalizado y han normalizado que te
taking that
quiten esa
a lot from you they have normalized it and that's it
barbaridad la han normalizado y punto
Why Because there are more people who don't
Por qué Porque hay más gente que no lo
earn it than they do so there are more
gana que sí lo gana entonces hay más
people like this Pablo mour envious
gente así como este Pablo mour envidiosa
who prefer that those who earn that
que prefieren que los que ganan ese
money those who  They manage to earn that
dinero los que consiguen llegar a ganar
money they prefer to have it taken away from them
ese dinero prefieren que se lo quiten
because they can't stand that there are people
porque no pueden soportar que haya gente
who have that profit, they leave,
que tengan esa ganancia qué se van por
why don't they leave, why such a thing? Well, I gave a
qué no se van por qué tal bueno di un
speech that I considered very appropriate
discurso que yo consideré muy apropiado
for the moment we were living in and that is why
para el momento que estábamos viviendo y
this debate makes no sense. Let's
por eso este debate no tiene sentido se
put it in the area of ​​Why are they leaving and How can we
ponga en Por qué se van y Cómo podemos
solve it? There are people who are self-employed and
solucionarlo hay gente que es Autónoma y
entrepreneurs who do not earn what I earn
emprendedora que no cobra lo que cobro
and are completely suffocated by the
yo y va completamente asfixiada con los
taxes they are subjected to. When the focus of
impuestos que le ponen cuando el foco de
the conversation is on that point and not
la conversación esté en ese punto y no
on someone saying what a son of a [ __ ] is
en que alguien diga qué hijo [__] que se
leaving Andorra, well, that's a moment it
va andorra pues ahí es un es un momento
's a logical thing, but since
es una cosa lógica pero como los
politicians are not capable of doing that and
políticos no son capaces de hacer eso y
neither is popular opinion, it makes no
tampoco la opinión popular no tiene
sense to talk about that subject. You understand, there
sentido hablar de ese tema entendéis se
has been a lot of fighting with a youtuber
ha peleado bastante con un youtuber que
called Felipe 360 ​​and Felipe, to what he
se llama Felipe 360 y felipez a lo que
said, okay, let's start there, the next thing. Of
puso vale empezamos por ahí el siguiente
course, because I ate
trasto Claro porque me he comido aquí la
gref's response to the thread here, then.
respuesta de gref a el hilo entonces
This is going to another
Esto va para otro
mouse, well, let's see the truth, I'll give
ratón bueno a ver la verdad vuelvo a dar
the context again, we are on the 2nd,
el contexto un poco estamos a día 2
now January 3rd. Okay  It's already January 3rd,
ahora 3 de enero Bueno ya es 3 de enero
my sister's birthday, I love you
el cumpleaños de mi hermana te quiero
sister eh The Movida is that
hermana eh La Movida es que ha empezado
the year has started quite hectic, I find
el año bastante Movidito me encuentro
that today as I leave I think it was
con que hoy tal y como salgo creo que ha
leaving the hotel already filling the
sido saliendo del hotel ya llenando el
car the suitcases and when I think it
coche las maletas ya cuando creo que ha
was when I left the Hotel, Fran sends me
sido cuando he salido del Hotel me manda
a WhatsApp on one hand and
un WhatsApp por un lado el Fran y por
Pablo on the other okay on one hand Fran sends me
otro el Pablo vale por un lado me manda
a WhatsApp saying to me, you see, you
un WhatsApp el Fran diciéndome verás tú
see, I'm going to open Go to Twitch
verás tú voy a abrir Vete para Twitch
that I'm going to open Twitch and I'm going to mess
que voy voy a Abrir Twitch y voy a liar
something up and I [ __ ] wait until tonight but of
una y yo cabrón espérate a la noche pero
course Franco This is
claro Franco Esta es
like, of course I was going to tell you about some
como como claro qu te iba a decir algún
wild animal that I have in the
animal salvaje que tuviera en el
sanctuary but of course lately
santuario pero claro últimamente nada
I only see capí baras and peacocks and the
más que veo capí baras y pavos reales y
occasional otter I hope it continues like this
alguna que otra nutria Espero que siga
Fran During the next few months that
así Fran Durante los próximos meses que
I'm going to be there I hope there's not
voy a estar yo por allí Espero que no
a tiger or anything like that
haya por ahí un tigre ni nada por el
no but of course Fran is like that no I
estilo no pero claro Fran es así no O
mean you can't stop him then
sea no lo puedes frenar entonces de
suddenly by the time I was
repente para cuando yo le estaba
answering the whatsa dude he was already
contestando al whatsa tío ya estaba
cursing everything on Twitch and I didn't  I've
cagándose en todo en Twitch y no lo he
seen I imagine that they've
visto me imagino que por aquí me habrán
put a
puesto un
summary for me But well Salado really big has
resumen Pero bueno Salado bien gordo se
gotten into a really big mess and has
ha liado bien gordo y ha papeado
absolutely eaten I've seen a tweet in
absolutamente yo he visto un tweet en el
which he tramples on wismichu I mean but he
que pisotea wismichu o sea pero lo
tramples on him at the wismichu level who the [ __ ]
pisotea a nivel wismichu quién [__] Te
sends you to get into these things If you
manda a que te metas en estas cosas Si
're not even dedicating yourself to this
ya no estás ni dedicándote a esto para
why who the [ __ ] sends you I mean above all it's
qué quién [__] Te manda o sea sobre todo
not I mean when you know that they're going to
es eso no O sea cuando sabes que te van
respond to you with that but well he has
a responder con eso pero bueno se se ha
taken out Win michu and he has taken out
cargado a Win michu y se ha cargado a
Felipe in a pl pl with seven bad words
Felipe en un pl pl con siete palabrota
But well it has gone down well with gucho ad
Pero bueno se ha cado bien a gucho ad
quite a bit with a youtuber named
bastante con un youtuber que se llama
felipez 360 and felipez to what he put It's that
felipez 360 y felipez a lo que puso Es
I'm going to analyze this as
que yo esto lo voy a analizar como
simply reading it as the gossip of the
simplemente leyéndolo como el salseo del
moment of 2024 but it's very heavy that it
momento de 2024 pero es muy heavy que
's because of us I mean no no provoked
sea por nosotros O sea no no provocado
by me yes
por mí sí
Ah or so
Ah o sea que
indirectly the
indirectamente lo de
Ah shut up I didn't know that detail they
Ah calla que ese detalle no lo sabía a
sent me Felipe's tweet yesterday
mí me mandaron ayer el tweet de Felipe
but I was on vacation I haven't  you
pero estaba de vacaciones no he cuenta
know I would have finished it Today I would have
sabes se lo hubiera terminado Yo hoy
sent it to Fran 100% okay Win michu it's
mandando a Fran 100% vale Win michu es
too ridiculous Win michu already
demasiado ridículo Win michu ya es que
what am I going to tell you about Win michu No well well the
ya qué te voy a decir yo de Win michu No
only thing I can tell you Wi
pues pues lo único que te puedo decir Wi
michu is that he has a trial very
michu es que tiene un juicio muy
soon that they haven't said anything about or rather
prontito del que no han dicho nada o sea
I can't stop seeing his mother-in-law telling
yo no paró de ver a la suegra contando
details of the trial she had
detalles del juicio que ha tenido
with me okay And contacting all these
conmigo vale Y contactando con todas las
hater Twitter accounts and
cuentas estas de Twitter de hater y ella
herself and and contacting all
misma y y contactando con todos los
these channels that are against
canales estos que están en contra de
Dallas to say that she had a
Dallas para decir que que ha tenido un
trial with me how she held her
juicio conmigo que cómo llevaba las
hands how I how we argued anyway she has
manos que cómo me me como discutimos en
been telling details of the trial
fin ha ido contando detalles del juicio
but she doesn't tell the one about her son-in-law that he has
pero no cuenta el de su yerno que tiene
one Very soon very important and no no no I haven't
uno Muy pronto muy importante y no no no
heard it anywhere I know that he
lo escuchado en ninguna parte se eso se
has surely forgotten that tomorrow faca faca he will
ha olvidado seguro que mañana faca faca
surely bring it out okay well there are more things
lo saca seguro vale bueno ha más cosas
that have happened that he has
que han pasado de las que se las ha
forgotten about too well We will have to
olvidado también bueno las Tendremos que
tell them soon but that La Movida It's that
contar prontito pero que la La Movida Es
indirectly this starts with
que indirectamente esto empieza por lo
Lilo but yes talking about me [ __ ] I
Lilo pero sí hablando de mí [__] me
was  it's hard to [ __ ] today no matter how
estaba costando [__] hoy por mucha
hard I tried nothing came out and now I
fuerza que hiciera no salía nada y ahora
understand fate you the tweet that
lo entiendo fate tú el tweet que pone
Felipe puts to refute what
Felipe para rebatir lo que está diciendo
Fran is saying I mean Fran is talking about what
Fran o sea Fran está hablando de de lo
Fran is talking about
de Fran está hablando de lo de los
taxes and all that nonsense an
impuestos y todo el rollo ese una
opinion based no and and it jumps at you
opinión basada no y y te salta
eh To discredit Fran eh [ __ ] I
eh Para desacreditar a Fran eh [__] me
was [ __ ] myself I was hard to [ __ ]
estaba [__] me estaba costando [__]
today no matter how hard I tried
hoy por mucha fuerza que hiciera no
nothing came out and now I understand my [ __ ]
salía nada y ahora lo entiendo mi [__]
had taken human form and I was
había tomado forma humana y estaba
writing from this
escribiendo desde la cuenta de este
guy's account I apologize I apologize for the damage
señor pido caus pido Perdón por el daño
caused by this tremendous pile of
causado por tremendísimo montón de
[ __ ] I mean look at the tweet Javi
[__] o sea fijaros el el tweet Javi el
Ali's trial when was
juicio del Ali cuándo era el juicio del
Ali's trial is in February if I remember correctly I mean
Ali es en febrero si no me falta Si no
look at the
me falla la memoria o sea fijaros el
tweet what argument is this what is it
twit qué argumentación es esta qué es lo
refuting
que rebate
exactly you know what now for
exactamente sabéis qué que ahora por
example if I lose a trial for
ejemplo si yo pierdo algún juicio por
calling someone a broom this will be one
decirle a alguien pelo escoba este será
of those who retweet it Ann as if
de los que lo retuitear Ann como
saying it is the most serious thing in the
diciendo que es lo más gravísimo del
world do you want to bet something I hope  doesn't have to
mundo queréis apostar algo Ojalá no
happen because I hope I
tenga que pasar porque ojalá no pierda
never lose a trial but well in which you
no nunca un juicio pero bueno en el
want to bet that in case I
queréis apostar que en el caso de que yo
lose by calling someone hair broom
pierda por decirle a alguien pelo escoba
this one is going to be the first one that's going to
este va a ser el primero que va a
share the
compartir la
news you want to bet that he's going to
noticia queréis apostar eso que va a
have the
tener los
balls I understand my [ __ ] had taken
[__] entiendo mi [__] había tomado
human form and I was writing from
forma humana y estaba escribiendo desde
this guy's account I apologize for
la cuenta de este señor pido perdón por
the damage caused by an incredible pile
el daño causado por tremendísimo montón
of [ __ ] of course you put this to Fran Cuesta
de [__] claro a Fran cuesta le pones
and Fran Cuesta loses his
esto y a Fran cuesta se le va la
answer I don't know you But you say that your
contesta no te conozco Pero dices que tu
[ __ ] transformed into me in
[__] se transformó en mí como forma
human form if that were the case you wouldn't be someone
humana si fuera así no serías alguien
that could have been and it wasn't someone who
que pudo ser y no fue alguien que se
looks in the mirror and knows who he was is and
mira al espejo y sabe que fue es y
always will be ugly with an unpleasant asp
siempre será feo con asp desagradable
someone who without another person
alguien que sin que otra persona le
attacking him tries to attack him someone who
ataque le intenta atacar alguien que
lives locked up in his [ __ ] because he's not
vive encerrado en su [__] porque no es
who he would have liked to be
quien le hubiese gustado ser En
Ultimately talking about [ __ ] someone
definitiva hablando de [__] alguien
who isn't worth the [ __ ] he shits
que no vale ni la [__] que
[ __ ] [ __ ] okay or whatever Fran puts
caga [__] [__] vale o sea Fran le pone
that tweet to him quite a bit like for me but
ese tweet bastante like para mí pero
well it would catch him offside I wouldn't
bueno le cogería fuera de juego No
know who this guy is probably
sabría quién es este tío seguramente
[Music]
[Música]
and I  I'm seeing something but I'm not
y me esto estoy viendo una cosa pero no
going to comment on it because it's already
la voy a comentado porque ya es entrado
in another topic. This was
en otro tema esta ha sido la respuesta
Felipe's response. Maybe I didn't understand well, let's
Felipe igual no se me ha entendido bien
see Frank. How do I explain it to you?
a ver Frank Cómo te lo
[Music]
[Música]
Hi Javi. Happy New Year and greetings to
Hola Javi Feliz año nuevo y saludos a
cacahuete who will watch this video. Cacao 4
cacahuete que verá este video cacao 4
Love. Cacao 4 Love. Cacao 4 Love. A
Love cacao 4 Love cacao 4 Love un
kiss. Maybe I didn't understand well, let's
beso igual no se me ha entendido bien a
see Frank. How do I explain it to you?
ver Frank Cómo te lo
[Music]
[Música]
You're a [ __ ] [ __ ] this is the
Eres un [__] subnormal es la
answer. Put on a t as if to say, Look how
respuesta ponete t como diciendo Mira qu
based Alex El capo supports him,
basado Alex El capo lo apoya claro
of course,
evidentemente
the effort of making that
el esfuerzo de hacer ese
video is totally dude,
vídeo totalmente tío
d, answering Alex El capo, that Alex
d respondiéndole Alex El capo eso Alex
shows the story that you are by hanging out
demuestra la hisoria que eres juntándote
with, do you remember when Alex El
con os acordáis cuando la ex del Alex El
capo's ex started
capo se puso a
commenting, started commenting that Alex
comentar se puso a comentar que el Alex
El capo watched
El capo veía en privado
utbh's videos privately and all
los vídeos de utbh y todos los canales
these anti-progress channels, not secretly, but
estos anti progress no a escondidas pero
he publicly continued pretending that he was
él públicamente seguía fingiendo que era
prog. I'm going to read you the ones that
progr voy a leeros los que me han
seemed
parecido más
strongest to me, this is a  a little bit of history
fuertes esto es un poco lo el historial
so you can see why he answers like that
para que veáis por qué da las contesta
okay Javi A curious fact about all this
así vale Javi Dato curioso de todo esto
is that shad I don't know if you remember him
es que shad no sé si recuerdas de él
well he posted a tweet in support of
bueno él puso un tweet en apoyo al vídeo
Felipe's video but he deleted it and asked for
de felipes pero lo borro a las y pidió
forgiveness it seems the guy didn't know where he had gotten himself into
Perdón se ve que el man no sabía dónde
XD
XD
yes he did put a t and deleted it well he gets
sí puso un t y lo borró pues se lleva
my goodness Well a little bit of context for
madre mía Bueno un poco del contexto de
this is okay look at what Felipe did
Esto vale fijaros lo que hacía Felipe
with Dallas okay before seeing the other
con Dallas vale antes de ver el la otra
little thing or more hypocritical Hey, that Dallas
cosita o más hipócrita Oigan que Dallas
has left Twitter is not a
haya marchado de Twitter no es una
victory it would be if they had closed
victoria lo sería si le hubieran cerrado
his account permanently what Cool
la cuenta de forma permanente qué Guay
no Felipe that people lose their jobs let's
no Felipe que la gente pierda su trabajo
see I imagine that you have noticed
a ver imagino que os habéis dado cuenta
people were already doing a lot
ya estaba la gente haciendo un montonazo
of spam and things putting links like
de spam y de cosas poniendo enlaces de
these of seeing the subscribers at the
estos de de ver los suscriptores en el
time of Dallas because of the move that
momento de de Dallas por la movida que
has happened now and such And this man Well
ha habido ahora y tal Y este hombre Pues
in an attempt to do damage control
en un intento de hacer control de daños
eh he has put the subscribers in hidden
eh ha puesto los suscriptores en oculto
that you can do because there are no
que lo puedes hacer pues porer que no
subscribers So now you
haan los suscriptores Entonces ahora te
go to these  pages and they don't work they
vas a estas páginas y no funcionan se
can be done but there is one thing that I
pueden hacer pero hay una cosa que me
thought was very nice and that is that you
pareció como como muy bonito y es que le
give it at the moment in which you give it does
das en el momento en el que le das hace
this look here you
esto mira aquí
give it to
le le das a
Li it
Li
is very nice to see in the end it will happen
es muy bonito de ver al final va a pas
eh incredible a disgrace but then they
eh increíble una desgracia pero luego
have tweets like this in which Look
tienen tweet como este en el que Mirad
what they ask people like ad
lo que le piden a personas como ad
Dallas or like me to do of Felipe
Dallas o como a mí que hagamos de Felipe
not only that he dedicated this
no solamente que le haya dedicado esta
horde of tweets to Dallas because he
horda de tweet a Dallas porque haya
had some kind of personal problem
tenido algún tipo de problema personal
with him or something like that we can
con él o algo por el estilo podemos
find many tweets of the same
encontrar muchísimos tweet del mismo
caliber to other users for example to
calibre a otros usuarios por ejemplo a
salseo youtuber salseo youtuber But there
salseo youtuber salseo youtuber Pero
was a strong guy here He calls
había uno fuerte tío aquí lo Llama
Dallas an abuser we can talk about whatever comes out
Dallas podemos hablar de lo que salga
the balls we can't talk about Dallas
los [__] no podemos hablar de Dallas
because among the list of things that I don't
porque entre la lista de cosas que no me
find funny is number
parecen graciosas se encuentra número
one
uno el
abuse end of the list ent everything go
maltrato fin de la lista ent todo ir
better bullets that Dallas took advantage of a
mejor balas de las que se aprovechaba
long time ago he would have hit his head
Dallas tiempo atrás le hubiera cabeza a
at least Write well that the
hostias por lo menos Escribe bien que
[ __ ] goes with h and if this gentleman dasco
hostias va con h y si este señor dasco
Also his own followers
También dan asco sus propios seguidores
and people who support him are disgusting  to these kinds of
y gente que apoya a este tipo de
people what he said about
personas lo que dijo de la familia de
ariann's family no there wasn't a tweet in which he
ariann no no había un tweet en el que
said is that you should see this video
decía es que Este vídeo lo tendríais que
okay But there was a tweet in which he
ver vale Pero había un tweet en el que
literally said that he would be happy if
decía literalmente que se alegraría de
someone killed Dallas and his entire
que alguien matara a Dallas y a toda su
family
familia
no let's see
no a ver
Eh This is ad Dallas telling him in the
Eh Esto es ad Dalas diciéndole en el
new park where I live there are
parque nuevo de donde vivo hay
instructions on how to treat
instrucciones sobre cómo tratar la
[ __ ] let's fix our thing
[__] arreglemos lo nuestro
Dallas for people like Dallas is what I
Dalas por gente como Dallas es lo que
consider that preventive murder should be legalized
Considero que debería legalizarse el
if tomorrow the news came out
preventivo si mañana saliera la noticia
that a madman escaped from the rocket
que se ha escapado un loco de al cohete
and killed Dallas and his entire
y se ha cargado a Dallas y a toda su
family I would dance with joy okay that's what it is that's
familia bailaría del gusto vale eso es
him against Dallas
lo que es la eso es de él contra Dallas
okay Already part of the twi that have
vale Ya parte de los twi que la hayan
released it today okay But that's him against
sacado hoy vale Pero eso es de él contra
Dallas look at the type of character he
Dallas fijaros el tipo de personaje que
is
es
eh it's true man I hadn't realized
eh es verdad tío no me había dado cuenta
notice that the video has 7000 dislikes
fijaros que el vídeo tiene 7000 dislikes
man that is 7000 people who support this
tío o sea 7000 personas que apoyan esto
man what how disgusting man how disgusting you eh
tío qué qué asco tío qué asco tú
Oh [ __ ] I have it
eh Ay [__] que lo tengo
stopped he says the same story  that they
parado dice la misma historia que me
did to me in 2017 if you
hicieron a mí en 2017 si te
notice they all seem like clones in appearance
fijas todos parecen clones en apariencia
and
y en antecedentes
criminal records okay And here Win michu enters the
penales vale Y aquí Win michu entra en
scene No of course eh they get along
en escena No claro eh ellos se llevan
they are friends
bien ellos son amigos
and you will
e
understand after the videos that I have
entenderéis después de los vídeos que os
shown you about Dallas and others no that
he enseñado sobre Dallas y demás no que
I do not know if Felipe in reality Because I
yo no sé si Felipe en realidad Porque yo
see a certain tone of Ela in Felipe Win
a Felipe le veo cierto tono de Ela Win
michu like a certain flattery I do not know like he
michu como cierto peloteo no sé como que
idolizes him okay well overall Win michu
lo idolatra vale bueno total Win michu
thinks this is great It is the best that the
le parece esto genial Es lo mejor que
internet Spain has given us and that's it
nos ha dado internet España y ya
Win michu thinks this is the best
está a Win michu esto le parece lo mejor
that the internet Spain has given it
que le ha dado internet
ta a
ta un
kiss and Fran answers Win michu
beso y Fran le contesta Win michu
certainly between you showing
ciertamente entre tú mostrando tetas de
girls' tits on the internet and this Felipe 360
niñas en internet y este Felipe 360
saying that we have to [ __ ] girls
diciendo que hay que follarse a niñas
thanks to the fame of the internet you
gracias a la fama de internet
are surely top 10 on the internet
seguramente seáis top 10 de internet
Spain in your field okay and give the
España en lo vuestro vale y dar el
applause no what a burial you should
aplaude no menudo enterramiento deberías
think about opening a funeral home because
pensar en abrir una funeraria porque
you are the best at it
eres lo mejorcito en ello
eh wismichu dude besides
eh wismichu tío además
and this has not been answered okay This
e ya esto no ha respondido vale Ya esto
has not been answered wismichu I know  has
no ha respondido wismichu se me ha
come to mind He always tells me it's
venido a la cabeza Siempre me dice a mí
not that you announce this lawsuit and you don't
no es que tú anuncias esta demanda y no
file it I don't know what Win michu dedicated himself
la pones no sé qué Win michu se dedicó
for a time to sending him
durante una época a mandarle
Ah well I'm not going to say it or if I'm not
Ah bueno no lo voy a decir o si no lo
going to say it I'm not going to say it I'm not going to say it I'm keeping it to myself I'm
voy a decir no lo voy a decir no lo voy
keeping it to myself I'm keeping it to myself You're going to be left wanting you
guardo me lo guardo Vais a quedar con
know No Well let's see if I
las ganas sabes No Bueno a ver si lo
can say it if
puedo decir si es que realmente lo ha
he really said it in public it's not something else
dicho él en público tampoco es otra cosa
no but he dedicated himself to warning a
no pero se se dedicó a a advertir a
lot of youtubers I don't know Even if with
muchos youtubers no sé Incluso si con
buran no and things like that to a lot of
buran no y cosas de esas a un montón de
youtubers that he was going to sue them
youtubers de que los iba demandar
okay You know and I think that of course I
vale Sabes y yo creo que claro me
remember that even when he won the
acuerdo que incluso cuando el le gana la
lawsuit against nauter which was for insults
demanda a nauter que era por insultos
for insults he put up a thread saying
por insul tios puso un hilo diciendo
well a Well this is the first then
pues a Pues a este es el primero luego
all the others I have sued and also I
todos los demás he demandado y además
think he said I have even sued
creo que dijo incluso he demandado a
five or six youtubers he said of course he hasn't
cinco o seis youtubers dijo claro no ha
sued anyone Well I think he has
demandado a nadie Bueno creo que ha
sued someone but for insults
demandado a alguien pero por insultos
too no no I don't know because no no I do
también no no no lo sé porque no
n't know  a lot of that demand but
no no sé mucho de esa demanda pero ya se
the cani tillero already took care of putting it okay
encargó el cani tillero de ponerlo vale
but the thing is that the thing is that he does
pero la movida Es que la movida es que a
n't sue those who have said the strong things to him And it's like why don't you
no lo demanda Y es como por qué no lo
sue him damn Those are the things
demanda [__] Esas son las cosas que
you have to sue sue him damn you know
tienes que demandar demándalo [__] sabes
Those are the things you have to
Esas son las cosas que tienes que
sue but of
demandar pero
course but no no no no
claro pero no no no no
but why the
pero
[ __ ] do they get into this if they know that
para qué [__] se meten esto si sabe que
cane tillero is going to get caught who will that
pillar cane tillero quién será esa
account be that knows everything about that about that
cuenta que sabe todo sobre esa sobre esa
part no no no yes yes I mean cane tillero
parte no no no sí sí O sea cane tillero
took and and and starts announcing
cogió y y y se pone a anunciar las
Win michu's lawsuits also you know it's
demandas de Win michu también sabes que
like who
es como quién
will be good well this is another thing
será bueno pues esto es otro otra cosa
that I have taken which is basically this is
que he cogido que es básicamente esto lo
put by F wismichu hid more than 100 tweets
pone F wismichu ocultó más de 100 tweets
responses to later close the
respuestas para posteriormente cerrar el
tweet so that nobody else can comment or
tweet y que nadie más pueda comentar o
rather
sea
eem
eem por lo
apparently people have started to comment
visto la gente ha empezado a comentarle
in response to wismichu because of the
en respuesta a wismichu por cosa de los
charrues no Let's see let's see how well you
charrues no A ver vamos a ver qué bien
defend yourselves
os defendis
between you are not happy or anything Uy uy  oh oh oh
entre no estáis contentos ni nada Uy uy
[ __ ] my god between you [ __ ] defending yourselves
uy uy uy [__] madre mía entre [__] os
hide the answers whatever the
oculta las respuestas que quiera el
past wants You can't anymore [ __ ] the one they
pasado Ya no puedes [__] la que le
're giving
están dando
him garbage with the garbage It doesn't
tú la basura con la basura No
fail
falla
[ __ ] [ __ ] they're putting it fine
hostias [__] lo están poniendo fino
eh God of my
eh Dios de mi
life of course the move with hiding
vida claro es que la movida con ocultar
this of hiding the The
esto de ocultar la La
answer is eh
respuesta es eh
[Music]
[Música]
my god I don't even dare to read it man
madre mía no me atrevo ni a leero tío de
how strong the twi are that this thing of
lo fuerte que son los twi que esto de
hiding the answer in the end it looks
ocultar la respuesta al final queda como
worse because
peor porque
[Music]
[Música]
you hide the
la tú ocultas la
answer and on Twitter the icon appears that
respuesta y en Twitter sale el icono de
the user is hiding a tweet that they
que el usuario está ocultando twit que
don't want people to see So in the
no quiere que la gente vea Entonces al
end it gives more exposure to those you
final le da más difusión a los que
want to hide than if you
quieres ocultar que si los
ignore them you understand my
ignoras me entendéis el
point I mean the issue of hiding the
punto o sea el tema de ocultar las
answers I see it even
respuestas yo lo veo hasta hasta
worse And why would it look worse because
peor Y por qué quedaría peor porque
Twitter by putting the icon there so
Twitter al poner el icono ahí para que
you can see the tweets that it has hidden gives it
tú veas los tweets que ha ocultado le da
more exposure and people come in to see
más difusión y la gente entra para ver
what it is that you're hiding let's see I'm going to see
qué es lo que ocultas a ver voy a a ver
when you see here in the corner the T
cuando veas aquí en la esquinita el T
says let's see I'm going  let's see what she's
dice a ver voy a ver qué es lo que
hiding, what she's
oculta qué es lo que le da
ashamed of, do you understand me? I mean, she should
vergüenza me entendéis o sea debería
have the option to hide the
tener la opción de ocultar la
answer but the tweets shouldn't be seen,
respuesta pero que no se vieran los
mandarin effect? ​​Are you
tweet efecto mandarina me estáis
understanding my point or not? It's
entendiendo el punto o no
as if it's separate from the fact that it's
es como que queda aparte de que queda
credited
acreditado
in the tweets that you've
em los twi que has
hidden? Look at her mother-in-law supporting
ocultado mira su suegra apoyando la
Wismichu's mother-in-law also supporting
suegra de wismichu apoyando también a
Felipe.
Felipe
Man, Ángelis Ara. What a beautiful day,
Hombre ángelis ara Qué bonito día la
really. I hope people continue to open their
verdad Ojalá la gente siga abriendo los
eyes to the scum of the internet. I
ojos con la scoria de internet
understand that this thing about Angeliz Sara is
entiendo que esto de angeliz Sara es en
against Felipe Wismichu,
contra de Felipe wismichu
of course. I don't know
claro No sé
if you understood what I mean about hiding the
si si me habéis entendido lo de ocultar
t's, but I see it a little like that. I
los t pero lo veo un poco así O sea yo
mean, I wouldn't put that on Twitter
es que eso no lo pondría en Twitter
directly, and this thing about Ricky Edy. No, I
directamente y esto lo de Ricky edy No
haven't commented on it anyway. Calling
que lo he comentado igual Llamar nas a
a woman who made dark humor a nas in an
una tía que hacía humor negro en la
era where it was fashionable to be a Nazi isn't
época donde la moda era ser nazi no es
the best strategy if you're someone
la mejor estrategia si eres alguien
proud of having posted a
orgulloso de Haber puesto tweet de
pedophile tweet at the same time. And that
pedófilo en la misma época Y eso no
wasn't fashionable, but what do I know if
estaba de moda pero qué sabré yo si no
I'm nothing more than a fascist.  evader eye
soy más que un facha evasor ojo que
both cases seem like [ __ ] [ __ ] to me
ambos casos me parecen una [__] [__]
but being progressive can't be used as an
pero ser progre no puede utilizarse como
excuse for having made a fool of yourself in the
excusa para haber hecho el tonto en el
past and on top of that being proud of
pasado y encima estar orgulloso de
tweeting such a savagery let's see It's that
twitear esa salvajada a ver Es que la
thing and that's why I corrected the tweet and there were
movida y por eso he corregido el tweet y
people telling me Uh I don't know what we're
había gente diciéndome Uh No sé qué
going to see The Thing that Ricky
vamos a ver La Movida que aquí Ricky
says here both cases seem like [ __ ] to me
dice ambos casos me parece una [__]
let's see the
vamos a ver
Nazi thing is a [ __ ] kid's [ __ ] that
lo de nazi es una [__] gilipo de crío
everyone did it but Win
que lo hacían todos pero lo hacía Win
michu did it Felipe did it jager
michu lo hacía Felipe lo hacía jager lo
everyone did it and we brought it out at the time they
hacían todos y lo sacamos en su momento
wore mustaches they dressed up they said
se ponían bigotes se disfrazaban decían
stupid things they were jokes okay what
tontería eran bromas vale lo de lo de
Felipe did is not normal I mean I think Felipe's thing
Felipe no es normal o sea creo que lo de
has absolutely nothing to
Felipe no no tiene absolutamente nada
do with the other one posting
que ver con lo de que la otra pusiera
Nazi stuff okay these people who are raging at
nazis vale esta gente que está furando a
sarabin apart from him
sarabin aparte de él
wait Look at the tweets okay let's
espérate Mira los tweets vale vamos a
see a little bit of the tweets I can almost
ver un poquito de los tweet casi puedo
see the boys and girls with the poster
ver a los niños y niñas con el póster
spread out on the floor spraying it with their
extendido en el suelo rociándolo con sus
young
jóvenes
fluids auron Play That's because now
fluidos auron Play Eso es porque ahora
you're a  dirty homosexual who doesn't insult
eres un sucio homosexual que no insulta
girls
a niñas
[ __ ] is like riding a bike
[__] es como montar en bicicleta lo
your thing is to learn with your father when you were
suyo es aprender con tu padre de
little on F B a foreigner told me I
pequeño en el F B una guiri me dijo que
looked like a huggable guy and I didn't rape her
parecía un tipo abrazable y no la violé
on the
en el
spot call me the [ __ ] from me
acto llama la [__] de mi
auron fame on YouTube should be used
auron la fama en YouTube debe usarse
to sleep with girls not actresses porn no do
para tirarse a niñas no actr el porno no
n't dishonor us you know they are all
no nos des honres sab es que son todos
in the same tone you know
en el mismo en el mismo tono sabes
So what does this have to do
Entonces esto que qué tiene que ver esto
with the Nazi joke because the
con lo de la broma nazi porque lo de la
Nazi joke if it is understood it is not understood
broma nazi si se entiende no se entiende
that it is an [ __ ] it is understood that it is not
que es una gilipo se entiende que no es
literal that you are not a Nazi literal no that it is not it is
literal que no eres nazi literal no que
understood that it is not serious you
no es se entiende que no es en serio
know but this is repulsive this is
sabes pero esto es repulsivo esto se
supposed to be a joke boy 21 shy
supone que es un chiste chico 21 tímido
sensitive I
sensible
dream of [ __ ] on a 14 year old girl's chest
sueño con cagarle en el pecho a una niña
single
de 14 soltero
Call me I was alone with two panchitas I
Llámame estaba solo con dos [__]
saw them wanting to name me their
las veía con ganas de nombrarme su
shaman masturbating thinking about babies
chamán masturbarse pensando en bebés no
is not a crime if you only use your
es delito si solo lo usas tu
imagination yes the n if he did it this one
imaginación sí lo de n si lo hacía este
too and they all did it I
también y lo hacían todos o
mean this is  tremendous
sea este es tremendo
eh I mean they all did it you know and now they
eh o sea lo hacían todos sabes y ahora
tell me when I put that Stream
me dicen cuando he puesto ese Stream me
some of them told me No but it's that I saw what Deisa
decían alguno No pero es que ví lo deisa
and it's like yeah but it's that Felipe isn't
y es como ya pero es que felipes no está
telling villin all day about Itaa
diciendo a villin todo el día lo de itaa
Felipe is still telling him about the
Felipe le está diciendo a día de hoy
Nazi thing
nazi lod
Taisa I was on the call in which
taisa yo estuve en la llamada en la que
both of them well And Auron also
ambos ambas bueno Y auron también
got on well with her in fact then after a few
quedaron bien con ella de hecho luego al
days I remember that It Taisa
cabo de los días me acuerdo que it taisa
asked me to ask Auron for
me me pidió que le pidiera a auron
a video for her son too anyway eh
también un vídeo para su hijo en fin eh
because she had a son look you choose the
porque tenía un hijo fíjate tú elijo el
smallest Auron superfan and he made
más pequeño superfan de auron y le hizo
Auron a video Well Auron sent it to me
a auron un vídeo Bueno me lo mandó auron
so I could send it to her anyway
para que se lo mandara a ella en fin
[Music]
[Música]
e But anyway watch out because there in the group There's
e Pero bueno ojo porque ahí en el grupo
someone I don't know if Felipe but they
Hay alguno yo no sé si Felipe pero que
also had jokes with Jeremy and with
también tenían bromas con Jeremy y con
Marta El Castillo I don't know if it was Felipe there's
Marta el castillo yo no sé si fue Felipe
one who is being given one
había hay uno al que le están dando una
too but anyway
también pero bueno
Eh I don't see that the cases are the same
Eh no veo que los casos sean iguales
obviously No it's not  for justifying
evidentemente No no es por justificar a
villin but I don't see that I don't see that they
villin pero no veo que no veo que que
are even
sean ni
similar
parecido
Oh me too supporting
Ah mi también apoyando a
Felipe Celin
felipes celin
too little princess
también princesita
too they start supporting Felipe
también se ponen a apoyar al Felipe
dude they start supporting Felipe
tío se ponen a apoyar
Felipe I love you
felipes Felipe Te quiero
very much I totally agree it's okay to
mucho Totalmente de acuerdo está bien
clean up from time to time if there are
hacer limpieza de vez en cuando si hay
people who insult me ​​for giving my
gente que me insulta por dar mi
opinion eh hi I'm already cool now I'm
opinión eh hola Ya estoy chado ya ya soy
more or less a person I have a PC and
más o menos persona tengo m el PC y
well the camera that is in the kitchen
bueno la cámara que está en la cocina
is a real pain but now I'll
está hecho todo un [__] pero ahora me
get going and then I do it directly before
pongo y luego hao directo que antes de
closing this magnificent arc of the beginning
cerrar este magnífico arco de principio
of the year I wanted to leave a little
de año quería dejar una pequeña
reflection is that or rather it can give me vertigo
reflexión es que o sea puede dar vértigo
I just realized that I am
me acado cuenta de que estoy a cont
backlit it's going to look like [ __ ] good
contraluz se va a ver como el culo bueno
boy but what's in front is not going to be seen
chico peror que lo deante no se va a ver
and it can give vertigo to the people of my
e puede dar vértigo a la gente de mi
guild it can get wet in certain
gremio puede al vértigo mojarse en según
things because of the [ __ ] that can
Qué cosas por la [__] que te pueda
fall on you I don't know do you have any idea how I have
caer no sé hais una idea de cómo tengo
the mentions right now full of
las menciones ahora mismo llenas de
absolute garbage
absoluta basura
but I would like to emphasize one thing All
pero me gustaría recalcar una cosa Toda
this [ __ ] that falls on me is from  out And that
esta [__] que me cae es de fuera Y eso
's irrelevant like on the internet there are
es irrelevante en plan en internet hay
a lot of people you don't have to be liked by
mucha gente no tienes que caerle bien a
everyone Now there are a lot of people who
toda la gente Ahora hay mucha gente que
think things about me that are quite
se piensa cosas de mí que están bastante
far from reality but the thing is that those
lejos de la realidad pero es que esa
people at first are not Peña who wants me to be
gente de primeras no es Peña que quiera
reading my tweets seeing my
que esté leyendo mis tweets viendo mis
[ __ ] stories or watching my streams or
[__] historias o viendo mis streams o
my videos it's people that I don't want to
mis vídeos es gente que no quiero que
even know that I exist so well what the [ __ ] do
sepa ni que existo entonces pues bueno
I care that a
pues qué [__] me importa que eso que un
17 year old kid with fascist ideas
chaval de 17 años con ideas filofascista
thinks that I'm a pedophile uploads
se piense que soy un pedófilo me suba
three [ __ ] balls
tres [__] [__]
crazy with Fil ist ideas
loco con ideas Fil istas
dude I mean
tío o sea
literally if you're against the
literalmente si estás en contra de de
t for example not
los t por ejemplo no de
Felipe you are fascist that That's the
Felipe eres filofascista esa Esa es la
answer it's already solved I don't care it's that I
respuesta ya está solucionado me da
couldn't care less
igual es que no pueda importarme menos
So that If there are things that
Entonces eso Si hay cosas que os
worry you and you think it's okay to take
preocupan y que creéis que está bien
advantage of your position to
aprovechar vuestra posición para
position and to
posicionar y para para
express Well that a vision of the world
expresar Pues eso una visión del mundo
that isn't as [ __ ] grim And horrible
que no sea tan tan [__] grim Y horrible
as what we're seeing
como lo que estamos viendo nuestro
around us that doesn't put you off the fact that there are
alrededor que no seos echa para atrás el
people who  go
el el que haya gente que se os vay a
throw on top because they are people who are not
echar encima porque es gente que no es
your people they are garbage So what does it matter
tu gente es basura Entonces qué más da
Ah they are not garbage people the thing is if Peña
Ah no es gente basura la cosa es si Peña
that you respect if Peña that you appreciate
que respetas si Peña que que aprecias te
tells you hey here you have gone too far Hey here you
dice oye aquí te has pasado Oye aquí te
have swung that is the point of
has columpiado ahí es el punto de
worrying But if he is telling you
preocuparse Pero si te lo está diciendo
that
eso
with those you have nothing to do with with
con la que no tienes nada que ver con la
whom you would not
que no
share Of course It is that the people that the
compartirías Claro Es que la peña que la
people that support him are people that
peña que le apoya son gente que le
support him but not because they think it is good for
apoyan pero no porque les parezca bien
sure Let's want to think that not because
segur Vamos quiero pensar que no porque
they think the things that
les parezca bien las cosas que hace
Felipe Jean Luis does are good they support him because of
Felipe Jean Luis un beso lo apoyan por
the things that Felipe does against other
las cosas que hace Felipe contra otra
people come on in fact I would dare to
gente vamos de hecho yo me atrevería a
think that there are people who are
pensar que hay gente que lo está
supporting him and are telling him well Felipe
apoyando y le está diciendo bien Felipe
what you do is very good
lo que tú haces está muy bien
simply because of the harassment tweets that he
simplemente por los tweets de acoso que
has sent to Dallas I mean
le ha puesto a Dallas
but they are people who accuse have
o sea pero son gente que acusa han
accused Dallas of things with minors and
acusado a Dallas de cosas con menores y
so on and that they have Dallas very disgusted
demás y que le tienen a Dallas muy asco
and we have to fight against Dallas for things
y hay que luchar contra Dallas por cosas
of minors and
de menores y
so on should seem very
demás debería parecerle muy
bad to him the things that Felipe says
mal lo las cosas que dice Felipe
no no I don't
no no
know a [ __ ]
no sé ni un [__]
bus what  [ __ ] it matters that's it I'm going to
autobús qué [__] importa ya está voy
put the computer on me Now we'll see
a poner a m el ordenador Ahora nos vemos
what's up Felipe 360 ​​How are you How's
qué pasa Felipe 360 Cómo estás Cómo va
life going Hey look yesterday all of a sudden out of the blue you
la vida Oye mira que ayer de repente sin
started
venir a cuento de no sé me empezaste a
calling me [ __ ] no that you called me
llamar [__] no que me llamaste
and and well I answered you normal not
y y bueno yo te respondí normal no
normal what's going on you
normal qué es lo que pasa que tú me
answered me with this video with this
respondiste con este vídeo con este
video maybe I wasn't understood well let's
vídeo igual no se me ha entendido bien a
see Frank How did you explain it to me
ver Frank Cómo te lo exp
[Music]
[Música]
and you're right in many ways in
y tienes razón en muchísimos aspectos en
many ways I am a [ __ ]
muchísimos aspectos yo soy un subnormal
okay but I'm going to tell you what
de acuerdo pero te voy a decir lo que
you are This is what this is what
eres tú Esto es lo que esto es lo que
you are masturbating thinking about babies is not a
tú masturbarse pensando en bebés no es
crime I dream of [ __ ] on
delito sueño con cagarle en el pecho a
a girl's chest
una niña
[Music]
[Música]
So you know Felipe each one of us already
Así que ya sabes Felipe cada uno ya
knows what we are I am a
sabemos lo que somos yo soy un
[ __ ] And you are what you are and you
subnormal Y tú eres lo que eres y
always
siempre lo
will be Well, on this side of Loren in
serás Bueno yo a esta parte del Loren de
fact he doesn't regret those t
hecho que no se arrepiente de esos t eh
eh I mean I think he justified them I
o sea creo que los ha justificado Yo me
remember that he already knows those t I think we
acuerdo que eso ya se lo esos t ya creo
got it out of him at the time and I think that  he
que se lo sacamos en su momento y creo
justified like well it was the
que lo justificó en plan bueno era la
time I don't remember what he gave I don't
época no me acuerdo lo que dio no me
remember exactly what he gave But he
acuerdo exactamente que lo que dio Pero
said crap it hadn't arrived and
dijo una porquería no había llegado y ya
I'm starting to feel a little a little
me empiezo a sentir un poco un poco
uncomfortable I'm starting to feel I'm starting to feel I'm
incómodo me empiezo a sentir me empiezo
starting to feel a little
a sentir me empiezo a sentir un poco
uncomfortable in fact wimus quoted This video
incómodo de hecho wimus citó Este vídeo
of Felipe It's the best thing the internet has given us
de felipez Es lo mejor que nos ha dado
and Fran answers him and it makes him
internet y Fran esta le contesta y le
certain I'm starting to feel a little
pone ciert empiez a sentir un poco
uncomfortable quote this video of why the
incómodo cit este vío de porque nos ha
internet has given us and Franco answers him
dado internet y Franco esta le contesta
and it makes him certain between you showing
y le pone ciertamente entre tú mostrando
tits of Well there you go guys there you go it came out it
tetas de Bueno ya está chicos ya está
came out a little on
que salía salía un poco en
Twitter how
Twitter qué
disgusting gibel gave him the dance of the year the
asco gibel le pegó el baile del año la
biggest humiliation of all and only
humillación más grande de todas y solo
Let's go two days Quesada Felipe is
Vamos dos días Quesada Felipe es
simply the typical
simplemente el típico [__] español
two-faced Spanish [ __ ] who also gives off a
doble cara que además desprende un tufo
hated stench moral superiority being the
aborrecido superioridad moral siendo lo
closest thing to a human wreck always
más cercano a un despojo humano siempre
on the right side of history honor
del lado correcto de la historia honor
francua It's that I don't see call either, let's have a
francua Es que yo tampoco veo call haya
doubt eh fan of Fran cuesta since he
duda eh fan de Fran cuesta desde
was little well there Agustín we have  that
chiquitito bien ahí Agustín tenemos que
going to the sanctuary to break our faces
ir al santuario a partirnos la cara
aus is that it is brutal but it is that I do not
aus es que es brutal sea pero es que yo
think so either or even if you
creo que tampoco o sea aunque te caiga
dislike francoa because I understand that there are
mal francoa porque entiendo que hay
people there who are supporting because they
gente ahí que está apoyando porque
want to go against franca but
quiere ir en contra de franca pero
even if you dislike franca that you dislike franca
aunque te caiga que te caiga mal
How are you going to get with
franca Cómo vas a ponerte con
Felipe I love to see Austin
felipes a mí me encanta ver al Austin
kid it is the
chaval es la
host the place putting me Ah clip in
[__] el lugar poniéndome Ah clip por
between Let's see [ __ ] qu without reading the
medio A ver cabrón qual sin leer el
tweet how is he going to support Felipe Of course
tweet qu tal va a apoyar a Felipe Claro
because he is one of his
porque es de los
own I am worried about
suyos me preocupa la poca capacidad de
people's poor reading comprehension
comprensión lect hor de la gente los twi
Felipe's tweets are obviously a joke
de Felipe son obviamente de coña
any adult brain should be
cualquier cerebro adulto Debería ser
able to discern the obvious then the
capaz de discernir lo obvio luego los
same ones will say it is that you can no longer make
mismos dirán es que ya no se puede hacer
humor about anything when they are not allowed to be
humor sobre nada cuando no les dejan ser
homophobic of course It is that you do not
homófobos claro Es que es que no
understand the joke damn and man and
entendéis el chiste [__] y yo tío y yo
man the best is going to support Franco
tío el millor va va a apoyar a Franco
is here the best does not fail me here the
estáa aquí el millor no me falla aquí el
best is one of mine Felipe
millor es de los míos Felipe
360 ​​nothing more exists F4 scc1 this is that
360 no existe nada más F4 scc1 esta que
a pr0  gre in the end both are eseer cal some
un pr0 gre al final ambos son eseer cal
s but it's that man, I don't see, I would not
unas s pero es que tío yo no a ver yo no
become friends or support
me haría amigo o apoyaría a una persona
such a disgusting person Simply because he is
tan asquerosa Simplemente porque se esté
fighting with someone with whom I am
peleando con alguien con quien yo estoy
against, I mean, I simply
en contra o sea pues simplemente me
put myself against both of them okay but it's
pongo en contra de los dos vale pero es
that these people their circle and everything
que esta gente su círculo y todo se
move on the basis of well Well this what a
mueven en base a bueno Bueno este qué a
thing Dallas well I support it even if it goes
cosa Dallas pues lo apoyo aunque vaya
completely against my
completamente en contra de mis
principles Well they have done it eh In
principios Bueno lo han hecho eh De
fact, many of the people who
hecho mucha de la gente esta que la
support her, the wiis michu the other and such
apoya el wiis michu la otra y tal se
are hanging out with youtubers who are
están juntando con youtubers que son
quite questionable happy new
bastante cuestionables feliz entrada de
year Javi in ​​2024 I wish you the best,
año Javi en 2024 Te deseo lo mejor
start things strong, that everything goes
empieza fuerte la cosa que todo te vaya
very well for you, up those
muy bien arriba esa
gentlemen says Lone exactly no no no but it's that
señoreros dice Lone exacto no no no pero
Lone you think you know everything and you
es que Lone os creéis que sabéis todo y
still don't know many things that I have not been
no sabéis todavía muchas cosas que no he
able to tell yet I am waiting
podido contar todavía me estoy esperando
a few days to tell it but they hang out
unos días para contarlo pero se juntan
with youtubers who are completely
con youtubers que que son completamente
contrary to what they preach or
contrarios a lo que ellos predican o
defend, I mean imagine that I am
defienden o sea imagínate que yo estoy
completely
completamente en
against it, it would be very complicated to
contra es que sería muy complicado
put you  an example that has the
poneros un ejemplo que que tenga la
gravity or is also
gravedad o sea además
Look, youtubers get together among themselves
Mira se juntan entre ellos youtubers que
maybe out of hatred for Javi Oliveira, out of
a lo mejor por odio a Javi oliveira por
hatred for Dallas, okay, but they get together among
odio a Dallas vale pero se juntan entre
themselves, youtubers
ellos youtuber
that both the youtuber does things that are
que tanto el youtuber hace cosas que se
supposed to offend them
supone que a ellos le
and the
como las
offended ones do things that the youtuber
ofendidas hacen cosas que al youtuber le
finds
parecen
disgusting but they get together among themselves
asquerosos pero se juntan entre ellos
even though they would kill each other originally If
aunque se matarían originalmente Si no
Javi Oliveira didn't exist, for me, I know
existiera Javi oliveira para yo que sé
that mu it is very regrettable that is
que mu es que es muy lamentable eso es
very
muy
regrettable the pharaoh It is
lamentable la faraona Es
true the pharaoh had to go to
verdad la faraona tuvo que irse a
Argentina for some similar things and to
Argentina por unos tets similares y
comment but it is
comentar pero es que es
normal now but of course the
normal ya pero claro es que la
pharaoh is that Felipe has people who
faraona es que Felipe tiene gente que lo
defend him that is what I do not
defiende que es lo que yo no
understand I do not understand let's see I understand that it
comprendo no lo comprendo a ver entiendo
will be because as he is getting involved
que será porque como se está metiendo
with francua Well, because of the people who are
con francua Pues por la gente que está
against him ideologically and he will also
en contra ideológicamente y también se
join Well, that he gets together with El capo
sumará Pues que se junta con al El capo
and that AC thing will get together in Dallas, I
y se juntará que AC cosa a Dallas me
imagine that it will go that way the reason nines
imagino que irá por ahí el motivo nines
a kiss I imagine that
un beso me imagino que irá por ahí el
Felipe's support will go there because I try to find the good in him and I don't understand Karime tells me, "Jou," did you send me a tweet from Felipe with his genitals exposed and that he tagged a minor? Yeah, well, let's see, I can't put it on screen, obviously I don't know
ponerlo en pantalla evidentemente no sé
if she was a minor compared to the girl
si era menor a la a la chica que
the roleplayer is tagging? He supports Felipe, man,
etiqueta el roler apoya a Felipe hombre
of course,
claro
logical, I understand.
lógico
No man, no, no. Let's see, wait,
entiendo No hombre no no A ver espérate
I'll have a coffee
que me echo un café
and this is
e esto es
sad. The
triste la parte
first part, I'm going to walk away because the noise
primera me vo a alejar porque el ruido
is the same, it's not a good idea. The
est igual no es una buena idea la parte
first part made me laugh, the video
primera esta me ha hecho gracia el vídeo
was funny and what do I know? I had a
me hacía gracia y yo que sé me lo he
good time. This second part is sad to
pasado bien esta parte segunda es triste
be a participant, seeing this in first
ser partícipe ver esto en primera
person is sad, please someone
persona es triste por favor que alguien
take away grandpa's phone because no, he doesn't
le quite el móvil al abuelo porque no no
understand how the internet works. There's no
entiende cómo funciona internet em no
need to put screenshots of these
hace falta que pongáis capturas de estos
old tweets of mine, they're in my account, they're
tweets viejos míos están en mi cuenta
still there because it seems to me like
siguen estando porque me parece có se
an analogy, the lamps that are like this,
una analogía las lámparas que están así
what do they do and they are, do you know, they
con que hacen y están como sabes que
attract flies and bugs and the
atraen a las moscas y los bichos y los
bugs come and die?  Well,
bichos llegan y se mueren pues son un
those tweets are a little bit like that. Ah, I
poco o eso esos tweets Ah creo
sincerely believe that you don't need more than to
sinceramente que no hace falta más que
have that to read them and realize
tenerla eso para leerlos y darte cuenta
that either they
de que o
're some kind of comedy that you're
son algún tipo de comedia del que estás
reading part of. Or they're going in that
leyendo una parte O o van por ahí los
direction like, I'm not going to tell you, it's not
tiros en plan no te vo a decir no es
black smoke. I was in another time, I was
humos negro yo era en otra época era
different, I'm not the same person, eh, or a
diferente no soy la misma persona eh o
lot of things have changed, but crazy. You don't have to
se ha cambiado muchas cosas pero loco No
be very, you don't have to be very sharp
hay que estar muy no hay que ser muy
to realize it, but oh
[__] afilado para darte cuenta pero
well, anyway, this is something
bueno e todas formas esto es una cosa
that isn't the first time and it's going to be the
que no es la primera vez y va a ser la
last time that happens to me, that the
última que me pase que vengan los
vultures come to try to dig up [ __ ]
buitres a intentar sacar [__] el año
last year when the Nazi from Vín thing happened,
pasado cuando pasó lo de la nazi de vín
eh. They've already arrived. Well, those people who
eh Ya llegaron Pues eso esta gente que
make a living off the Nazi from Vín, I
se dedica a vivir de la nazi de vín o
mean, with all their balls, with all their balls, with all their
sea con todo su huevo con todos sus
balls, the
huevos con todos sus huevos la
Nazi from
nazi de
Villin, I mean, their thing. It's a joke that they're
villin o sea lo suyo Es broma que son
twi that no, no, no, there's no, I don't understand. What's
twi que no no no hay no entiendo Cuál es
the joke in those tweets, but the Vin thing is a
el chiste en esos twet pero lo de vin es
real Nazi,
nazi de verdad
eh, generating absolute garbage on the internet and
eh generar absoluta basura en internet y
started trying to dig through my
empezó a intentar escarbar entre mis
tweets and  I said it seemed like an
tweets y lo dije me parecía un tema
interesting topic to talk about, like what the
interesante el hablar de eso de cómo era
internet was like 10 years ago and all that. And I
internet hace 10 años y tal Y que me
felt like talking about this and I did a
apetecía hablar de esto y hice un
live stream where I just spent the time
directo que simplemente me lo pasé
revisiting things that you see now and
revisitando cosas que las ves ahora y
say, damn, this is ugly, and going into a
dices [__] Esto está feo y entrando un
bit about whether there was an explanation for each
poco en en en si tenía explicación cada
thing or if I was just stupid at the
cosa o si simplemente era bobo en ese
time. It's a possibility, eh,
momento también Es una posibilidad eh
but no. I mean, these tweets, I mean, there must be
pero no O sea estos tweets o sea habrá
things of mine that are bad from over the years. I've been
cosas mías que sean malas de los años
here longer than the [ __ ]
llevo aquí más años que que las [__]
roads, but those tweets in particular,
carreteras pero esos tweets en concretos
Frank. I'm sorry to inform you that
Frank Lamento informarte de que son
each and every one of them are jokes taken
todos y cada uno de ellos bromas sacadas
from a time and
de de un momento y un
place, that's it. It's a
lugar
joke, of
broma
course. They're all comedies. The one with the guy
claro Son son todos comedia El del chico
so and so. That's the original, I don't remember,
tal Ese es que el original no me acuerdo
but I remember exactly that
pero me acuerdo exactamente de que
someone on the internet, I don't know if it's Angelis
alguien de internet no sé si angelis
Aras or someone, posted a tweet that was some
aras o alguien puso un twet que era una
[ __ ] with that same sentence format,
cosa gilipollez con ese mismo formato de
period sentence, period sentence, period. And
frase punto frase punto frase punto y lo
my thing was that same sentence changed to
mío era esa misma frase cambiándolo por
nonsense, for example,
barbaridades por ejemplo el la respuesta
Auron's response of I don't know what about not the girls such and such
auron de no sé qué de no las niñas tal
was because I think there was  a news that he
era porque creo que había una noticia de
was dating a porn actress
que estaba saliendo con una actriz porno
and then I responded by
y entonces yo le respondí haciendo
alluding to the fact that on the internet
alusión al hecho de que en internet la
people have historically ended up being
gente históricamente ha terminado siendo
pedophiles saying No man no fame
pedófilos diciendo No hombre no la fama
on the internet is not to ally with a
en internet no es para aliarse con una
porn actress it is to ally with a
actriz porno es para aliarse con una
child I just don't know if I have to explain
niña es que no sé si tengo que explicar
every [ __ ] joke 10 years ago dude they are
cada [__] broma hace 10 años loco son
jokes they are Well well you read it now
chistes están Pues bueno lo lees ahora
like this isolated And you say Ugh how average but you do
así aislado Y dices Uf qué regular pero
n't have to be very smart to read it and
no hay que ser muy listo para leerlo y
realize that it is a [ __ ] joke
darte cuenta de que es una [__] broma
a kiss cat things
un beso cosas de gato
welcome Anyways it shouldn't
bienvenido De todas formas no debería
surprise me because seeing
sorprenderme porque viendo las viendo
the things that this gentleman posts
las cosas que pone este caballero de
normally it's clear well in the
normal está claro pueso que o sea al
end we all saw a bit of an
final todos vimos un poco una cámara de
echo chamber in a bubble on the internet but the
eco en una burbuja en internet pero la
echo chamber that this gentleman has created
cámara de eco que se ha montado este
the amount of [ __ ] dented he
caballero la cantidad de [__] abollados
has around him and the things that they
que tiene alrededor y las cosas que le
say to him I guess there's no need to be
dicen supongo que no hay que
surprised but it seemed to me I'm going to
sorprenderse pero me ha parecido voy a
remove this it seemed genuinely
quitar esto me ha parecido genuinamente
sad to wake up and see this video The
triste despertarme y ver este vídeo La
truth So that's maybe Someone has to
verdad Así que eso igual Alguien tiene
go ahead and take away the grandfather's cell phone
que [__] y quitarle el móvil al abuelo
because  it's not a crazy plan I was having fun
porque no es plan loco me lo estaba
yesterday It's a shame this has left me feeling
pasando ayer Es una lástima me ha dejado
bad a bad feeling from saying
mal cuerpo esto mal cuerpo de eso decir
[ __ ]
[__]
you this person needs help Hey good
tú esta persona necesita ayuda Eh Buenos
morning I've had my coffee my things I mean but he
días tomado mi café mis cosas o sea pero
has the balls to call a Nazi there when
tiene huevo de decirle a nazi aí cuando
he also has the same jokes I mean
él también tiene las mismas bromas o sea
t I don't know what these people are like I don't
t Yo es que no sé que est gente alino no
know what's going on in their heads I don't
sé que tienen dentro de la cabeza no
understand I try I mean I try to understand
entiendo intento o seaa intento entender
people when we're seeing things
a la gente cuando estamos viendo cosas
about them and criticize them I mean not
sobre ellos y criticarle O sea no
base it Simply on the fact that I don't like someone
basarme Simplemente en que a mí alguien
or they make me reject okay if
me cae mal o me produce rechazo vale si
not I'm going to try to see their point you know
no yo voy a intentar ver su punto sabes
but I mean their point is that their thing, their thing is
pero o sea su punto es que lo suyo lo
disgusting that's a joke it's more than obvious
asqueroso eso es broma es más que obvio
that it is no no it's obvious that it's a comedy
que es no no es obvio que es comedia
but the Nazi of
pero la nazi de
villian s is already there
villin s ya
but there's nothing that pisses me off more than a
pero no hay cosa que más me joda que un
No it's that I don't know what they call you now if
No es que no sé cómo os llaman ahora si
progress or or hili progress you've done
progress o o hili progress habéis hecho
what you want and then now you play
lo que os da la gana y luego ahora vais
as allies you play as feminists you play as
de aliados vais de feministas vais de
lgbt you play as everything or Felipe I don't know
lgtb vais de vais de todo o Felipe no sé
what will your name be you've been too
cómo será tu nombre te has pasado de
smart you've been too smart and
listillo te has pasado del listillo y
besides I'm going to tell you something the big
aparte te voy a decir una cosa la gran
difference between you and me you call me
diferencia entre tú y yo me llamas
grandpa is that I have a lot of life You
abuelo es que yo tengo mucha vida Tú
have very little life a lot of life
tienes muy poca vida mucha vida
worked
trabajada
and a lot of life
e mucha vida
eh in many points di Wait wait Wait wait Wait that's it
eh en muchos puntos di Espera espera
wait the TV is off
espera la tele apagada
eh I mean what is this
eh O sea qué es esto
man the TV is
tío la tele
off I'm watching a lot of
apagada estoy viendo mucha
people I'm watching a lot of
gente
people watching the
estoy viendo mucha gente viendo el
live that aren't subscribed you I mean I'm
directo que no está suscrita tú o sea
mandatory mandatory all of you who
obligatoriamente obligatoriamente todos
are watching the [ __ ] live
los que estáis viendo el [__] directo
subscribe subscribe
suscribiros suscribiros
[ __ ] subscribe also things are coming watch out
cabrones suscribiros además se vienen
eh also things are coming watch out eh
eh además se vienen cositas que ojito eh
but man
pero hombre por
please I assumed that
favor daba por hecho que se estaba
people were subscribing and the thing is I'm
suscribiendo la gente y es que me estoy
watching here Pepe Pablo Antonio who
viendo aquí a Pepe a Pablo Antonio que
aren't
no están
subscribed press the subscribe button
suscritos pulsar el botón de suscribiros
different [ __ ] in the world of health
cabrones diferentes del mundo de salud
better and worse I'm 50 years old 52 years old
mejores y peores tengo 50 palos 52 palos
yes I'm a grandfather still no I thought you were going
sí soy abuelo todavía no yo creí que
to stop I thought  that you were going to stop boom I've
ibas a parar creí que ibas a parar pum
given you the zasca of the year That's the
te he metido el zasca del año Ese es el
[ __ ] zasca of the year that I gave you
[__] zasca del año al que te he metido
today very nice what you did with the
hoy muy bonito lo que hiciste con el
rice I don't know what you did it with But you can't
arroz no sé con qu lo hiciste Pero tú no
call me [ __ ] you
me puedes llamar subnormal a mí no
can't call me [ __ ] okay and
puedes llamarme subnormal de acuerdo y
if you call me that you have to give reasons
si me lo llamas tienes que dar razones
why I'm [ __ ]
por lo que soy subnormal yo sé por lo
I know why I'm [ __ ] in many facets of my life I've already told you I'm [ __ ] like everyone else So in many facets of my life I am [ __ ] but of course I don't have a resume like yours I may have done bad things in my life but not a
hecho cosas malas en mi vida pero no un
resume like yours and you call me
currículum como el tuyo y que me vayas
worthy now after having messed
de Digno ahora después de haberte metido
with me because I don't know you I
conmigo porque yo a ti no te conozco no
had no [ __ ] idea who you are but no
tenía ni [__] idea quién eres pero ni
[ __ ] idea and suddenly you tell me that I'm
[__] idea y de repente me dices que soy
the personification of [ __ ] or I don't know what the
la [__] personificada o no sé qué
[ __ ] Santo what I answered you about and
[__] a Santo de qué yo te contesté y
this morning I came across a video
esta mañana me encuentro con un vídeo
that you made that by the way your friend
que hiciste que por cierto tu amigo el
wismichu the anug The  Princess Alex The
wismichu el anug La Princesita Alex El
boss tells you that you are super based What does it
capo te dicen que estás super basado Qué
mean that they also
quiere decir que ellos también están de
agree that the girls from
acuerdo que a ti las chavalas de
Guadalajara that you liked were
Guadalajara que te gustaban eran las de
14 years old I continue continue
14 años
because one thing is to post a
sigo sigo porque una cosa es poner un
funny tweet another two another three but
twit gracioso otro dos otra tres pero
when you have a history full of
cuando tú tienes un historial plagado de
things where you talk about children minors
cosas donde hablas de niños de menores
babies I think you have a problem what
de bebés yo creo que tienes un problema
happens is that maybe you are
lo que pasa es que a lo mejor lo estás
covering it up now
tapando ahora
I have not called you a pedophile Of
yo no te he llamado pedófilo Por
course not the only thing I have
supuesto que no yo lo único que tengo
to post are the tweets that you posted
que poner son los tweets que tú ponías
The only thing I have to post is what
Yo lo único que tengo que poner es lo
you are were and will be Because if you
que tú eres eras y serás Porque si tú no
have not deleted those tweets it means that You
has borrado esos tweets quiere decir que
still agree with all that
Sigues estando de acuerdo con todo eso
irony dark humor I don't know I don't know I don't know
ironía humor negro no sé no sé no sé
to what extent it is dark humor to rape
hasta qué punto es humor negro violar
girls abusing underage girls I don't know
niñas abusar de niñas menores no sé
to what extent it can be dark humor
hasta qué punto puede ser humor negro
once well two bu three but and you
una vez bueno dos bu tres pero y tú no
have not wanted to leave it there why because
has querido dejarlo ahí por qué porque
you have to show your followers
tú tienes que demostrar a tus seguidores
or your people like wismichu wismichu you are
o a tu gente como wismichu wismichu eres
a coward always always always  you
un cobarde siempre siempre siempre
always always like the things that are
siempre siempre das Like a las cosas que
bad about me but you've never had the
ponen malas mías pero nunca has tenido
balls to send me a direct tweet you're
[__] a ponerme un tweet directo eres
a coward you're a coward then
un cobardica eres un cobardica luego
your mother in law your girlfriend and your cousin will come to
vendrá tu suegra tu novia y tu prima a
defend you which is very good but you're
defenderte que está muy bien pero eres
a coward and today I put a t on you
un cobardica y hoy te he puesto un t
because you say that you have to tell your
porque dices que le tiene que decir a
mother in law what to tweet when you
suegra lo que tiene que twitear cuando
tell her and you send it to her Felipe
se lo diga y se lo mandes lo pone Felipe
360 ​​puts it It's the best thing that's ever happened to the
360 Es lo mejor que le ha pasado a
internet in Spain wismichu the best thing that's ever
internet de España wismichu lo mejor que
happened to the internet in Spain What did
le ha pasado a internet de España Qué es
Felipe 360 ​​put and
lo que ponía Felipe 360 y lo que sigue
what does he continue to put out there of stupid things or when you had sex with girls you told them to show you their tits and then you showed them on the internet or when you had sex you tried to kill a guy with a bottle by hitting him over the head What's the best thing about the
botellazo en la cabeza Qué es lo mejor
internet What's the best thing that's ever
de internet Qué es lo mejor que le ha
happened to the internet you or Felipe 360 ​​and the
pasado a internet tú o Felipe 360 y las
things that haven't come out yet
cosas que todavía no han salido
princess it's very good that you challenge
princesita está muy bien que retes
when they call me [ __ ] it's very good
cuando me llaman subnormal está muy bien
me  The follow if you can last anj what a
me la sigue si poder dura anj qué
shame man what a shame such an ally
vergüenza tío qué vergüenza tan Aliado
that you are and there there with your friend
que eres y ahí ahí con tu amiguete
Felipe 360 ​​and Alex El capo How lazy we
Felipe 360 y Alex El capo Qué vasados
all are but then what I'm going to
estamos todos pero luego lo que voy a
tell you is that apart You are a liar you
decirte es que aparte Eres un mentiroso
are a manipulator a liar and a
eres un manipulador un mentiroso y un
manipulator and don't manipulate me and don't
manipulador y a mí no me manipules y no
lie about me when you want to say
mientas sobre mí cuando quieras decir
something about me you say it with proof like
algo sobre mí lo dices con pruebas como
I have done like I have done
yo lo he hecho como yo lo he hecho
Felipe 360 ​​I don't know what I've read
félipe 360 No sé lo que yo he leído
about the girls you like from
sobre las chavalas que te gustan de
Guadalajara is that they were 14 years old I've
Guadalajara es que tenían 14 años he
seen that jerking off to a baby
visto que hacerse una paja con un bebé
is not a crime Of course not that's what
no es delito Claro que no eso es lo que
I see of you What do you see of me what they
yo veo de ti Tú qu ves de mí lo que
say what they say I'm not going to say
dicen lo que cuentan yo no voy a decir
what they say about you I say what it is and
lo que cuentan de ti yo digo lo que es y
many people are thinking But why do you
mucha gente está pensando Pero por qué
answer these people because these
le contestas a esta gente porque esta
people are the ones who pretend to be saviors of the
gente son los que van de salvadores del
world and they are [ __ ] hypocrites who
mundo y son unos [__] hipócritas que
have a past Blacker than hell
tienen un pasado Más negro que la [__]
and they are hiding it well they don't
y lo están escondiendo bueno no lo
hide it it's that they don't  they hide, I mean they
esconden es que no lo esconden o sea es
cover each other up, you know they don't
que se se tapan entre ellos sabes no lo
hide it, it's like it's not humor. It's okay, it
esconden es como no es humor Está bien
's humor and it's like, man, if you
es humor y es como tío pero si le habéis
made a house of br of a witch, even
hecho una casa de br de bruja incluso
talking to the girls, so that to
hablando con las chavalas para para que
send him what to tarle with the with
para mandarle lo que tarle con la con el
Dallas, I mean, with Dallas, it was tremendous what they
Dallas o sea con el Dallas fue tremendo
did to Dallas by
lo que le hicieron al Dallas poniéndose
agreeing You put this, you put the other thing, I
de acuerdo Tú pon esto Tú pon lo otro yo
have this group, you put this, you only
tengo este grupo tú pones esto tú solo
send this so that you
mandas este para que lo
challenge it and now Dallas was being
retu y ahora lo al Dalas lo estaban
condemned by the entire internet and calling the
condenando todo internet y Llamando a la
press, their friends in the press to
prensa a los amiguitos de la prensa para
put news about him,
que pusieran noticias sobre él
no, and now this is not that this, this is
no y ahora est no es que est este es
humor, this is humor, this is good people,
homor este es homor este es buena gente
This is one of
Este es de lo
us when what they are is what they were
nuestro cuando lo que son es lo que eran
and is what they will always be. Felipe 360 ​​You're
y es lo que serán siempre Felipe 360
always going to try to justify yourself, and
Siempre vas a intentar justificarte y
what you just said, you don't even believe it,
esto que acabas de decir no te lo crees
you're seeing how you justify yourself in
ni tú estás viendo cómo te justificas de
a [ __ ] way so that people
una [__] manera para que la gente te
tell you it's not true, it's true, it's sad,
diga no es verdad es verdad es triste
please someone take grandpa's cell phone away
por favor que alguien le quite el móvil
because you're not coming  you and
al abuelo porque no vienes tú y se lo
take it from grandpa why don't you come and
quitas al abuelo por qué no vienes tú y
take it from me Why don't you come and take it from me What's
quitas Por qué no vienes tú y me lo
happening that I can't tweet now what's happening
Qué pasa que no puedo ttear ya qué pasa
that I can't have freedom of
que yo no puedo tener libertad de
expression like you then you're going to
expresión como tú luego tú me vas a
call me everything fascist I took
llamar de todo fascist le quite el móvil
grandpa's phone I don't know what the [ __ ] you're calling me you
al abuelo no sé qué [__] me llamas tú
know what fascism is silencing
sabes lo que es el fascismo el callar a
others if they don't think like you come and
otros si no piensan como tú ven y
take it from me you are not a threat you said to
quítamelo tú no es una amenaza has dicho
take grandpa's phone Come
que le quiten el teléfono al abuelo Ven
and take it from me my children are in my
y quítamelo tú vijos míos están en mi
account stay here let's
cuenta sigan estando vamos a
justify ourselves come on let's
justificarnos venga vamos a
justify ourselves from those with dozens and
justificarnos de los de las decenas y
dozens of
decenas de
tw There everyone deleted their tws and I Juan
tw Ahí todos borraron sus twe y yo Juan
speak for you and I Juan if I'm not mistaken
hablo por ti y yo Juan si no me equivoco
went to Dallas with some story and
fue le fue al Dallas con algún cuento y
spoke to him Oh I don't know what But what's going on did
le habló Ay no sé qué Pero qué pasa te
Javi tell you something You know I don't remember I do
ha dicho Javi algo Sabes No me acuerdo
n't remember exactly what it
no me acuerdo exactamente queé lo que
was but I Juan got scared of the dasas
fue pero yo Juan se acoon todo del dasas
and deleted Well, I mean Juan almost got down
y borró Bueno o sea el Juan casi se puso
on his knees so they wouldn't do a
de rodilla para que no le hicieran un
video please I don't know what and and he had to
vídeo por favor no sé qué y Y tuvo que
edit videos that he had uploaded where he
editar vídeos que tenía subido donde se
Met the dala he edited them with the
Met el dala los editó con el editor de
YouTube editor He cut them I don't know
YouTube Los cortó no sé s
what over there I have it on video Search
qué por ahí lo tengo en vídeo Buscar en
my main channel Javi your mic is
mi canal principal Javi tu micro está
down Hello hello it's not okay
abajo Hola hola no está bien
Hello over there I have a video of what delir
Hola por ahí tengo vídeo de lo delir
Juan I have it over there I mean I don't
Juan lo tengo por ahí o sea no me
remember well how the move was but he
acuerdo bien cómo fue la movida pero se
took it no I don't see because he didn't want
acojo no que no vea porque no quería que
Dallas to take him out talking about children
el Dallas le sacara hablando sobre niños
and minors and sex and I don't know what we're not
y sobre menores y sexo y no sé que no s
going to justify ourselves come on you don't
vamos a justificarnos venga que no hace
need more than to have that to read them and
falta más que tenerla eso para leerlos y
realize that you understood it properly
darte cuenta de que lo entendido amente
Maybe other people won't finish that
A lo mejor otra gente no terminará eso
not to tell you it's not black I was in
no te decir no es unos negro yo era en
another time it was different I'm not the same
otra época era diferente no soy la misma
person eh I mean a lot of things changed
persona eh o sea cambiado muchas cosas
but it's what I told you you were You are and
pero es lo que te he dicho eras Eres y
always will be the same last year
serás siempre el mismo el año pasado
when the Nazi of Vín happened
cuando pasó lo de la nazi de vín
eh when the Nazi of Villin happened
eh cuando pasó lo de la nazi de villin
you all realize that you're still the
tú tod te das cuenta que sigu siendo el
same the Nazi of Villin then you go from
mismo la nazi de villin luego vas de
ally and feminist and all this
aliade y de feminista y de todas estas
[ __ ] with all these not because you call him
[__] con todos estos no por le llamas
born to vin she belonged to the
nacia a vín ella pertenecido al partido
Nazi party because villin is
nazi porque a villin se la tien en
sworn to because villin has made peace
jurada porque villin ha hecho las pases
with Dallas Fran And then villin
con el Dallas Fran Y entonces a villin
he has to go along with the
él le tiene que seguir el rollo a los
others to whom
otros a los
in short those who are his idols for
que en fin los que son sus ídolos para
him I imagine I don't know what move but eh ví
él me imagino no sé qu movida pero eh ví
made peace with Dallas and did not
hizo las pases con el Dallas y no
participate in that Dallas had to be burned
participó en que había que quemar al
So he is outside of them and
Dallas Entonces está fuera de ellos y
they when they are at dinners he told it
ellos cuando están de cenas lo contó lo
ketal I mean ketal himself
contó ketal o sea el propio ketal lo
told it once I don't know if I have the
contó una vez no sé si lo tengo la
call but Quetzal I have it around here eh
llamada pero Quetzal tengo por ahí eh
quetzal did
quezal hizo
a live where he said that Wi michu
un un directo donde contaba que Wi michu
and the miad the
y la miad las
meals how
comidas qué
strong
fuerte
man has happened
tío ha pasado una
something I can't believe what happened
cosa no doy crédito a lo que ha pasado
man a kiss
tío un beso
John the video is loud and not to me well
John se escucha alto el vídeo y a mí no
really I mean I can't
pues que de verdad O sea yo no puedo
upload this anymore let's see I could upload it
subir más esto a ver lo podría subir
but it would sound
pero se escucharía
ugly Hello hello
feo Hola
what did you put  Twitch yeah like you what happens
que puso Twitch sí como tú lo que pasa
is that he already came out he apologized he
es que ya salió pidió disculpas se
explained himself And you're still 13 that's the big
explicó Y tú sigues en tus 13 es la gran
difference general absolute garbage on the
diferencia general absoluta basura en
internet and Felipe started trying the
internet y empezó a intentar Felipe la
garbage is generated by you when you say that I
basura la generas tú cuando dices que yo
read out there that what you want are the ones
Leo por ahí que lo que quieres son la
you like are the 14 year olds in
que las que te gustan son las de 14 en
Guadalajara you can take out videos of me
Guadalajara tú puedes sacar vídeos míos
saying stupid things cursing at everything
diciendo burradas cagándome en todo
messing with people Eh saying the
metiéndome con gente Eh diciendo Las
biggest barbarities or insulting look at
mayores barbaridades o insultando mirate
the last video of little princess for
el último vídeo de princesita por
example okay you can call me filthy you
ejemplo vale me puedes llamar guarro me
can call me grandpa you can call me
puedes llamar abuelo me puedes llamar
dirty You can tell me that I don't have a
sucio Me puedes decir que no tengo ni
[ __ ] clue about animals, how to live anything
[__] idea de animales de vida de nada
but show me things Show me I
pero demuéstrame cosas Demuéstramelo yo
'm showing you Paula a
te lo estoy demostrando Paula un
kiss
beso
no I can't believe it man I can't believe it I can't give it credit I
no no puedo dar crédito tío no puedo dar
really can't give it credit I have to make
verdad no puedo dar crédito me tengo que
sure tomorrow maybe I can
asegurar mañana a lo mejor os lo puedo
tell you I
contar
've already shown you it's there well
Yo ya te lo he demostrado está ahí pues
for you it's a joke but for
para ti es una broma pero para la gente
normal people I repeat for normal people it
normal te repito para la gente normal no
's not a joke it's not a joke that you
es una broma no es una broma que tú
say that it's good to do what it is  Okay
digas que es bueno hacer que es Okay
jerking off because it's not a crime with a
hacerse pajas porque no es delito con un
baby Felipe 360 ​​Seek help that's not
bebé Felipe 360 Busca ayuda eso no es
a joke Seek help all this [ __ ]
una broma Busca ayuda toda esta [__]
comes at you for your tweets comes at you for your acting like an
te cae por tus tweets te cae por tu ir
ally of acting like a Super modern
de aliade de ir de Super moderno
defender of all the rights of
defensor de todos los derechos de todo
everyone that is that you even defend the
el mundo que es que defendis hasta los
rights of those who sell onions that you're not
derechos de las de las cebollas que no
even worth taking up the ass I mean eh
vales ni para tomar por culo o sea eh
Look I'll compare it to you I had a fight
Mira te lo comparo yo tuve una movida
with the best he's worth the best the
con el millor vale el millor el despojo
human waste that I call it That one has a
humano que le llamo yo Ese sí que tiene
lot of people you you're a bastard
mucha gente tú tú eres un desgraciado
How many people are watching you 1000
Cuántas personas te están mirando 1000
people are
personas te
watching you 1000 people were watching him
miran 1000 personas le estaban viendo
Talking about his I mean him fighting with
Hablando de su o sea él peleándose con
Franco 1000 people were watching this one
Franco este lo estaban viendo 1000
and he's the protagonist of the
personas y él es el protagonista de la
controversy what you were and what you are eh
polémica lo que eras y lo que eres eh
And what was it When was it what Felipe
Y qué era Cuándo ha sido qué Felipe
When was it
Cuándo ha sido
nothing the mother who gave birth to me Well then that
nada la madre que me parió Bueno pues
the best for example 4000 people see him
eso que el millor por ejemplo le ven
5000 people for example he's one of the ones I
4000 5000 personas por ejemplo es uno
fought with  okay the only
con los que me peleé vale la única
difference is that he was an [ __ ]
diferencia es que é era un [__]
like me an idiot like me but you
como yo un subnormal como yo pero tú
are something else Okay I don't want him to even
eres otra cosa Vale que no quiero que
know that I exist so
sepa ni que existo entonces
well God doesn't even know that I
bueno que no sabe ni Dios que
exist Even if he wants to even if they want they don't
exist Aunque quier aunque quieran no
know that they exist he's posting my
saben que existen está poniendo mi
live oh she's a friend of his that's fine fine he
directo ah es una amiga de él eso está
can post it on my
bien está bien lo puede poner en mi
live eh it doesn't matter if it is it doesn't matter I'm
directo eh da igual si es que da igual
going to take action we are on
que voy a tomar medidas estamos en
Twitch we are on Twitter they can post it
Twitch estamos en Twitter pueden poner
they can use it apart from the I mean him
pueden utilizarlo aparte de la O sea él
being the protagonist of the controversy
siendo el protagonista de la polémica
with Fran he was with a
con Fran él estaba con
thousand the girl I don't know if he said
mil la chica a mí no sé si me ha dicho
anything to me but I know that she's his friend I know that she
algo pero sé que es amiga de él sé que
's his friend okay [ __ ] I don't give a [ __ ] dude
es amiga de él vale la [__] me suda
but let's see
tres [__] [__] loco pero vamos a ver
if you give a [ __ ] Why do you
si te suda tres [__] [__] Por qué
have four videos and then a text
llevas cuatro vídeos y luego un texto
But why do you give a [ __ ] for
Pero por qué si te suda los [__] para
more people to attack me for
que se me eche más gente encima por
saying that I'm far right son of a
decir que soy de extrema derecha hijo de
[ __ ] look at it look at it because what you
[__] mírelo mírelo porque lo que me
're throwing at me is all that scum I'm a
estás echando es toda esa gentuza soy un
Boomer I'm not a Boomer [ __ ] me  I'm not
Boomer no soy un Boomer subnormal yo no
a Boomer I was before the
soy un Boomer yo soy antes de los
boomers I'm not a Boomer what's that you
boomers yo no soy un Boomer que es que
seem stupid if you don't even know how to
pareces tonto si es que no sabéis ni
speak if you don't even know the
hablar si es que no sabéis ni la
technology it's that I don't know why you
tecnología es que yo no sé por qué te
call yourself a pedophile you
llamas pedófilo tú a ti mismo tú te
consider yourself a pedophile because you
consideras un pedófilo porque tú ahí
say there that I should have called you a
dices que te tenía que haber llamado
pedophile and that there you would file a
pedófilo y que ahí me pondrías una
complaint against me If I don't call you a pedophile I
denuncia Si yo no te llamo pedófilo yo
only post some tweets that you're very
solo es puesto unos tweets que estás muy
proud of having them because you say that it
orgulloso de tenerlos porque dices que
's humor that it's humor jerk off eh
es humor que es humor hac se pajas eh
Looking at a baby say it's humor to say
Mirando a un bebé di que es humor decir
that the girls from Guadalajara that you
que las chavalas de Guadalajara que te
want to [ __ ] are 14 years old say it's
quieres [__] tienen 14 años di que es
humor eh that he's looking for a 14
humor eh que está buscando una de 14
year old to [ __ ] say it's humor that they
años para [__] di que es humor que
leave the fluids on top of a poster I don't
dejen los fluidos encima de un poster no
know It doesn't seem like humor to me that's it but I
sé A mí no me parece humor ya está pero
don't call you a pedophile no no everyone who
no te llamo pedófilo no no cada uno que
evaluates when people see me say
evalúe cuando la gente me ve a mí dice
This is a [ __ ] This is an imbecile he does
Este es un subnormal Este es un imbécil
n't have  I have no [ __ ] idea You're not a storyteller at all
no tiene ni [__] idea De nada es un
This is happening because of you and
cuentista Esto está pasando por ti y el
me exposing those tweets and that past
que yo exponga esos tweets y ese pasado
that is in the present and from what I
que está en en el presente y que por lo
see will continue in the future because if it
que veo seguirá en el futuro porque si
is now and you're proud it will continue in
está ahora y estás orgulloso seguirá en
the future you put that there you
el futuro eso lo has puesto tú lo has
did it and you have to
hecho tú y que tú te tengas que
justify yourself so much why do you have to
justificar tanto por qué te tienes que
bring in that cowardly villain again Little
meter otra vez a villin cobardica
Princess er the feminist is not from you
Princesita er el feminista no de estás
What did she do to him you
Que qué le ha hecho eso lo defiendes
also defend that you also defend that people
también defiendes también que la gente
can jerk off looking at babies
se puedea hacer pajas mirando bebés
Because it's not a crime anuj the same
Porque no es un delito anuj lo mismo
Alex The boss the same I don't mess with
Alex El capo lo mismo Yo no me meto con
anyone until they mess with me you
nadie hasta que no se mete conmigo tú
came to put [ __ ] on me you Felipe
has venido a meterme [__] tú Felipe
XIV came to put [ __ ] on me You
xiv has venido a meterme [__] Tú te
think I'm going to shut up because
crees que me voy a callar porque me
all the
vengan todos los
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
wismichu jitos and his [ __ ] mother come to me You
wismichu jitos y su [__] madre Tú te
think I'm going to shut up if like
crees que me voy a callar si como dices
you say I'm a grandfather who the [ __ ] there is
tú soy un abuelo quién [__] que haya
a grandfather I don't care that
un abuelo me da igual que lo haya
he wrote it who isn't  putting in
escrito él que no lo está colocando en
his tweet as a summary who tells me
su tweet como resumen quién me dice a mí
that he didn't write it I don't see the
que no lo ha escrito él yo no veo el
author Where is the author Where is the
autor Dónde está el autor Dónde está el
author let's see where is the author I don't
autor a ver dónde está el autor yo no
see the author it's his Twitter tweet that's the
veo el autor es su Twitter twite eso el
summary of what has happened and what it is
resumen de lo que ha pasado y lo que es
with which I do not retract any of
con lo cual no me retracto en ninguna de
the words because he is exposing himself
las palabras porque él está exponiéndose
there saying that I am far right that
ahí diciendo que soy de ultraderecha que
I am a Boomer that I am not a Boomer
soy un Boomer que no soy un Boomer
know once and for all I am not a
enterados de una [__] vez no soy un
Boomer I am from before the boomers it's
Boomer soy de antes de los boomers es
that I put them such and such you have not removed them are you
que los puse tal no los has quitado
proud of it you said it you are not
estás orgulloso de ello lo has dicho no
going to remove them I am not going to give my opinion here
los vas a quitar yo no voy a opinar aquí
who is right and who is wrong because the
quién tiene razón y quién no porque la
discussion is not about this Greg get wet
discusión no está en esto Greg mójate
[ __ ] you have been accompanying
cabrón llevas toda la noche acompañando
this gossip all night gref And now how are you
en este salseo gref Y ahora cómo no te
going to not get wet
vas a mojar
man how are you going to not get wet what past
tío cómo no te vas a mojar qué pasado
is Fran always well you see I mean it's that
está Fran siempre pues ya ves tú o sea
in any way man it is not something
es que de todas maneras tío no es algo
like unanimous I mean
como unánime O sea no tendría que ser
the opinion against Felipes should not be unanimous
unánime la opinión en contra de felipes
And these I mean no no  there are things in life that
Y estos O sea no no hay cosas en la vida
everyone
en las que todo el mundo se pone de
agrees on there are media cases that
acuerdo hay casos mediáticos en las que
everyone agrees on this would not be
todo el mundo se pone de acuerdo este no
one of them In which
sería uno de ellos En las que todo el
everyone should have an opinion that Exactly the
mundo debería opinar esa Exactamente
same I am simply shocked
igual yo simplemente estoy impactado de
that Fran de la jungla one of my
que Fran de la jungla uno de mis ídolos
television idols is fighting with
de la televisión se esté peleando con
Felipe and Felipe is saying that he
felipez y felipez esté diciendo que no
couldn't take a [ __ ] and Fran tells him that it is
podía [__] y Fran le diga que es una
[ __ ] but this is the beginning
[__] pero es que esto es el inicio
Felipe is fighting with Fran de la
felipez se esté peleando con Fran de la
jungla over a tweet that talks about me which
jungla por un tweet que habla de mí que
is Antonio Mur's with the days
es el de Antonio mur con los días
played in Fortnite in 2023 you
jugados en el fortnite en 2023 os dais
realize the twists and turns life takes And how
cuenta las vueltas que da la vida Y cóm
over time a Lore is generated
a lo largo del tiempo se genera un Lore
that you could never
que jamás te podías
imagine the bastard said something stupid
imaginar ha dicho una tontería el cabrón
and didn't take any action
y no se ha mojado
eh he said something stupid and didn't take any action
eh ha dicho una tontería el cabrón y no
F what are you telling me
se ha mojado F qué me estás diciendo
dude what are you telling me Sure,
tío qué me estás
sure not but
Claro claro no pero es que va va a
Cristina is going to sue eh I mean this guy this guy
demandar Cristina eh o sea el pipa
Today I posted it in a
este el pipa este hoy lo puse yo en un
TT
TT
also in a t I
además en un t lo
posted this pipa I don't know who it is I
puse el pipa este no sé quién es lo
hear it a lot lately it's a pipa with
escucho mucho últimamente es un pipa con
a with a verified okay And well the
una con un verificado vale Y pues los
seen like
vistos así como
the I don't know if it's the same one what the nu Or is
el no sé si es del mismo lo que la nú O
with the anu I don't know okay but it's
anda con el anu No lo sé vale pero es
like them Okay and I posted it today Look eh
como ellos Vale y lo puse hoy Mira eh
today pipa won't make any meme about
hoy pipa no hará ningún meme sobre
Felipe and puus in fact she has Ah By
Felipe y puus de hecho lo ha Ah Por
the way reeven told me reeven told me
cierto reeven me dijo reeven me dijo
about the princess conversation that
sobre la conversación de princesita que
in fact she is the one who threw chips at
de hecho es ella la que le tiró fichas a
him we have to clarify that reeven one
él eso lo tenemos que aclarar reeven un
day
día
eh from here reven we have to
eh desde aquí reven eso lo tenemos que
clarify that that is not possible that like this
aclarar eso no se puede que así
obviously this has to be clarified and I
evidentemente esto hay que aclararlo y
want that
quiero esa
conversation
conversación
a dick a
una [__] una
dick what is this what is
[__] qué es
this Javi ibay recommends
esto qué es esto Javi ibay recomienda el
Felipe's channel on his Twitch on his
canal de Felipe en su Twitch en su canal
Twitch channel on his profile Of course if they
de Twitch en su perfil Claro si es que
are friends I is not but I have
son amigos I no es pero eso ya lo he
said that many times eh I mean I is not from I
dicho muchas veces eh o sea I no es de O
mean ivai does not come from hanging out with auron
sea ivai no viene de juntarse con auron
with shoka  with many people think eh with
con shoka con mucha gente piensa eh con
gref I don't know what ivai has that group
gref no sé qué ivai ese grupo lo tiene
Now when it has grown but ivai is
Ahora cuando ha crecido pero ivai es de
Alex's The capo they were always together ivai
Alex El capo siempre estaban juntos ivai
Felipe Alex The capo and the Doo yv is from
Felipe Alex El capo y el Doo yv es de
those
esos
yv is that
yv es ese
group well La Movida that this pipa
grupo bueno La Movida que el pipa este
posted a tweet
puso un tweet
stating
afirmando
that Cristina seguí okay look he
que Cristina seguí vale mira lo ha
deleted it because he got scared Look Hi
borrado porque se ha acojonado Mira Hola
Cristina sorry for the inconvenience I
Cristina siento el inconveniente he
deleted the tweet important I just
borrado el tweet importante Acabo de
read that in my tweet it is understood that
leer que en mi tweet se entiende que
Cristina seguí published a video of a
Cristina seguí publicó un vídeo de una
woman being raped and it is not like that although she did
mujer siendo violada y no es así aunque
spread a video of the
sí que difundió un vídeo de la mujer
raped woman questioning her status as a
violada poniendo en duda su condición de
victim Sure but it is not the same
víctima Claro pero es que no es lo mismo
but come on it is not that Cristina seguí that they have
pero vamos no es que Cristina seguí que
already taken care of this Ah I have
esto ya se han encargado Ah lo he
closed it no
cerrado no
no they are in charge of challenging the
no se están encargando de retarlo los de
usual ones the ones you already know why they are
siempre los que ya sabéis porque están
against Cristina seguí because she is
en contra de Cristina segui porque está
with Fran because she is with Fran I mean
con Fran porque está con Fran me refiero
see if now you are going to tell me
a ver si ahora me vais me vais a decir
Oh Javi has confirmed the relationship I
Ay Javi ha confirmado la relación me
mean that she is with  he in like I don't
refiero que está con él en como yo no
and you've already seen Who are the ones who
e y ya habéis visto Quiénes son los que
have retweeted Cristina's thing and Who
han retuiteado lo de Cristina y Quiénes
have tweeted these days Oh Because Cristina
han twite estos días Ay Porque Cristina
has done such to attack Dallas eh I
ha hecho tal para atacar al Dallas eh o
mean they have used Cristina's thing to
sea han utilizado lo de Cristina para
attack Dallas and they are saying that
atacar al Dallas y están diciendo que
Cristina published a video of some minors And on
crisa publicó un vídeo de unas menores Y
top of that Cristina publishes on
es que encima Cristina lo que publica en
Twitter is a video that they publish
Twitter es un vídeo que ellas publican
on their Instagram saying Haha we are going to
en su Instagram diciendo Jaja vamos a
be famous we have lied And on top of that
ser famosas hemos mentido Y encima
Cristina spreads her face you know
Cristina le difunde la cara encima sabes
but oh well This is the
pero bueno Esta es la
move better watch the utbh interview
movida mejor vean la entrevista de utbh
because it is very clear there they
porque ahí queda clarísimo ahí lo
explain everything in detail
explican todo con detalles
Ah guys had more things to do but I
Ah chicos tenían más cosas que ver pero
have to go it's 3:30 we have been
me tengo que ir son las 3:30 nos hemos
away a long time with this issue and with the
lado mucho tiempo con este tema y con el
other tomorrow
otro mañana
we continue tomorrow we continue man
continuamos mañana continuamos tío
tomorrow I am going to have to be two longer live shows man I still have to do the
mañana voy a tener que ser dos directos
sacel thing and the
tío me queda pendiente lo de sacel y la
complaint and the whole thing man tomorrow I
denuncia y todo el rollo tío mañana
have to do a longer live show
tengo que hacer un directo más largo
because here we have already been for 2 hours and a bit
porque aquí ya llevamos 2 horas y pico
in the canijo on telesalseo too  I've
en el canijo en telesalseo también he
been here for 2 hours and a bit and I have to record
estado 2 horas y pico y tengo que grabar
videos so that telesalseo has videos
vídeos para que telesalseo tenga vídeos
and get into the swing of things. In fact, it would be ideal
y y ponernos a y [__] el ritmo de hecho
now to record videos for
sería ileal ahora grabar vídeos para
tomorrow for Teres salseo and tomorrow
mañana para teres salseo y mañana por la
morning to record newscasts would be
mañana grabar noticieros sería
ideal. I have to get into the swing of things. This this this
ideal tengo que [__] el ritmo que este
this month we're going to get our act together,
este este este mes nos vamos a poner las
man, the virus thing, everything,
pilas tío lo de virus todo todo
everything, I have a ton of topics prepared here,
todo me tengo aquí preparado un montón
man.
tío Pero bueno Mañana le damos
But anyway, tomorrow we'll give it a go, you'll have something Javi. No, no, no, this this this 2024, well, this January we're going to give the channels a real go, we're going to give all the channels a real go. What I don't know is if at some
los canales lo que no sé si en algún
point I'll upload the
momento volveré a subir los vídeos
edited videos and the edited reviews
editados y las críticas editadas en el
on the main page or I'll upload it right here, it depends. Do you dedicate more time to the kids than to the lady? No, more or less, eh. Same, more or less, I mean, the live show is more or less 2 hours, 3 hours in both places, both in one and
horas en los dos sitios tanto en uno
the other, and
como en el otro y
then the newscast on each channel every
luego el noticiero en cada canal cada
day. Same, more or less, depending on
día Igual más o menos que dependen de
the topics, depending on.  the news Never
los temas dependen de las noticias Never
Thank you very much it depends on the news and the
gracias depende de las noticias y de los
topics that there are okay And today there is for
temas que haya vale Y hoy hay para
kid cloth what yes I'm going to go
chaval tela lo que sí hace que voy a ir
now because I'm going to record some
ya porque voy a grabar unos cuantos de
videos for telesalseo of these of the
vídeos para telesalseo de estos de la
royalty and so on so that I have places
realeza y demás para que tenga lugares
to upload for tomorrow
para subir para mañana
and and that's it tomorrow I will try to return with
y y ya está mañana intentaré volver con
The news and I will return at full speed okay join
Los noticieros y volveré a tope vale
the WhatsApp group join
meteros en el grupo de WhatsApp meteros
the
en el grupo de
WhatsApp group because there I will announce all
WhatsApp porque ahí voy anunciando todos
the steps that I am taking Okay and we are
los pasos que voy dando Vale y estamos
at 300 subscribers
a 300 suscriptores
we are 300 subscribers on this channel
estamos a 300 suscriptores en este canal
from reaching
de llegar a
eh watch out watch out rest handsome a
eh ojito ojito que descanséis guapos un
kiss Thanks for the
beso Gracias por la
[Music]
[Música]
company
compañía